
export const staticQuizData = {
  "maths": {
    "easy": [
      [
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 76 + 187?",
            "answers": [
              "253",
              "261",
              "263",
              "264"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 263."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 324 + 337?",
            "answers": [
              "656",
              "661",
              "646",
              "660"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 661."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 409 + 175?",
            "answers": [
              "585",
              "569",
              "579",
              "584"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 584."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 85 + 53?",
            "answers": [
              "138",
              "153",
              "140",
              "137"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 138."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 391 + 122?",
            "answers": [
              "513",
              "498",
              "508",
              "511"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 513."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 185 + 290?",
            "answers": [
              "475",
              "474",
              "473",
              "460"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 475."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 56 + 253?",
            "answers": [
              "312",
              "309",
              "310",
              "319"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 309."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 241 + 311?",
            "answers": [
              "547",
              "562",
              "537",
              "552"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 552."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 137 + 221?",
            "answers": [
              "359",
              "357",
              "358",
              "361"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 358."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 248 + 343?",
            "answers": [
              "591",
              "588",
              "590",
              "576"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 591."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 56 + 230?",
            "answers": [
              "287",
              "283",
              "286",
              "289"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 286."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 303 + 441?",
            "answers": [
              "754",
              "741",
              "744",
              "759"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 744."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 324 + 277?",
            "answers": [
              "603",
              "602",
              "586",
              "601"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 601."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 148 + 60?",
            "answers": [
              "208",
              "207",
              "218",
              "206"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 208."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 50 + 105?",
            "answers": [
              "145",
              "160",
              "158",
              "155"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 155."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 92 + 271?",
            "answers": [
              "366",
              "363",
              "348",
              "364"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 363."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 64 + 215?",
            "answers": [
              "264",
              "279",
              "281",
              "277"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 279."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 62 + 377?",
            "answers": [
              "449",
              "439",
              "434",
              "440"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 439."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 240 + 392?",
            "answers": [
              "647",
              "629",
              "622",
              "632"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 632."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 325 + 206?",
            "answers": [
              "541",
              "529",
              "531",
              "526"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 531."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 323 + 222?",
            "answers": [
              "545",
              "535",
              "548",
              "555"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 545."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 271 + 81?",
            "answers": [
              "367",
              "347",
              "354",
              "352"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 352."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 495 + 428?",
            "answers": [
              "925",
              "938",
              "923",
              "933"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 923."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 131 + 317?",
            "answers": [
              "451",
              "448",
              "447",
              "443"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 448."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 329 + 421?",
            "answers": [
              "755",
              "749",
              "747",
              "750"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 750."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 309 + 174?",
            "answers": [
              "481",
              "482",
              "480",
              "483"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 483."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 150 + 308?",
            "answers": [
              "443",
              "455",
              "456",
              "458"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 458."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 92 + 224?",
            "answers": [
              "316",
              "311",
              "318",
              "319"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 316."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 447 + 64?",
            "answers": [
              "516",
              "526",
              "509",
              "511"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 511."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 164 + 480?",
            "answers": [
              "647",
              "644",
              "639",
              "649"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 644."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 225 + 406?",
            "answers": [
              "631",
              "646",
              "621",
              "636"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 631."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 235 + 392?",
            "answers": [
              "627",
              "624",
              "626",
              "628"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 627."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 470 + 142?",
            "answers": [
              "615",
              "612",
              "597",
              "613"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 612."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 238 + 85?",
            "answers": [
              "313",
              "323",
              "321",
              "326"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 323."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 76 + 350?",
            "answers": [
              "424",
              "426",
              "427",
              "416"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 426."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 174 + 381?",
            "answers": [
              "557",
              "553",
              "560",
              "555"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 555."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 306 + 344?",
            "answers": [
              "635",
              "650",
              "648",
              "649"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 650."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 269 + 388?",
            "answers": [
              "657",
              "672",
              "659",
              "652"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 657."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 290 + 327?",
            "answers": [
              "614",
              "612",
              "617",
              "616"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 617."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 411 + 347?",
            "answers": [
              "757",
              "758",
              "773",
              "743"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 758."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 496 + 179?",
            "answers": [
              "670",
              "673",
              "675",
              "676"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 675."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 360 + 56?",
            "answers": [
              "418",
              "411",
              "416",
              "426"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 416."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 318 + 134?",
            "answers": [
              "449",
              "455",
              "467",
              "452"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 452."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 164 + 194?",
            "answers": [
              "361",
              "358",
              "360",
              "348"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 358."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 375 + 250?",
            "answers": [
              "615",
              "626",
              "627",
              "625"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 625."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 439 + 384?",
            "answers": [
              "822",
              "824",
              "823",
              "826"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 823."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 149 + 158?",
            "answers": [
              "297",
              "307",
              "304",
              "292"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 307."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 261 + 385?",
            "answers": [
              "646",
              "645",
              "631",
              "649"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 646."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 407 + 199?",
            "answers": [
              "601",
              "604",
              "596",
              "606"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 606."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 158 + 313?",
            "answers": [
              "486",
              "456",
              "471",
              "470"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 471."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 262 + 163?",
            "answers": [
              "426",
              "425",
              "435",
              "428"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 425."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 249 + 89?",
            "answers": [
              "323",
              "336",
              "340",
              "338"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 338."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 114 + 112?",
            "answers": [
              "229",
              "228",
              "226",
              "225"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 226."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 197 + 235?",
            "answers": [
              "433",
              "429",
              "417",
              "432"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 432."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 353 + 390?",
            "answers": [
              "742",
              "758",
              "743",
              "733"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 743."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 264 + 114?",
            "answers": [
              "380",
              "373",
              "378",
              "363"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 378."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 66 + 100?",
            "answers": [
              "163",
              "161",
              "168",
              "166"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 166."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 80 + 78?",
            "answers": [
              "153",
              "148",
              "158",
              "160"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 158."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 233 + 275?",
            "answers": [
              "509",
              "508",
              "505",
              "507"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 508."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 199 + 217?",
            "answers": [
              "415",
              "426",
              "416",
              "417"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 416."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 331 + 83?",
            "answers": [
              "414",
              "404",
              "412",
              "411"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 414."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 451 + 359?",
            "answers": [
              "808",
              "810",
              "820",
              "813"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 810."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 239 + 370?",
            "answers": [
              "609",
              "594",
              "610",
              "604"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 609."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 403 + 480?",
            "answers": [
              "886",
              "883",
              "868",
              "882"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 883."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 90 + 243?",
            "answers": [
              "333",
              "328",
              "338",
              "348"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 333."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 425 + 355?",
            "answers": [
              "795",
              "777",
              "780",
              "783"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 780."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 148 + 155?",
            "answers": [
              "318",
              "302",
              "304",
              "303"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 303."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 248 + 63?",
            "answers": [
              "326",
              "311",
              "296",
              "309"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 311."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 144 + 101?",
            "answers": [
              "260",
              "245",
              "250",
              "240"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 245."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 87 + 234?",
            "answers": [
              "320",
              "306",
              "319",
              "321"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 321."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 97 + 367?",
            "answers": [
              "462",
              "454",
              "467",
              "464"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 464."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 459 + 460?",
            "answers": [
              "919",
              "917",
              "929",
              "921"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 919."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 479 + 107?",
            "answers": [
              "588",
              "576",
              "586",
              "591"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 586."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 469 + 117?",
            "answers": [
              "587",
              "583",
              "571",
              "586"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 586."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 116 + 461?",
            "answers": [
              "567",
              "577",
              "572",
              "580"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 577."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 448 + 249?",
            "answers": [
              "695",
              "682",
              "687",
              "697"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 697."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 186 + 341?",
            "answers": [
              "512",
              "530",
              "527",
              "537"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 527."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 355 + 330?",
            "answers": [
              "684",
              "670",
              "695",
              "685"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 685."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 500 + 152?",
            "answers": [
              "653",
              "654",
              "652",
              "649"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 652."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 493 + 459?",
            "answers": [
              "962",
              "947",
              "952",
              "937"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 952."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 346 + 147?",
            "answers": [
              "498",
              "508",
              "493",
              "494"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 493."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 88 + 475?",
            "answers": [
              "565",
              "553",
              "563",
              "560"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 563."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 409 + 65?",
            "answers": [
              "471",
              "474",
              "484",
              "459"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 474."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 415 + 75?",
            "answers": [
              "491",
              "505",
              "490",
              "492"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 490."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 379 + 386?",
            "answers": [
              "765",
              "766",
              "775",
              "755"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 765."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 127 + 386?",
            "answers": [
              "528",
              "508",
              "513",
              "523"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 513."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 411 + 184?",
            "answers": [
              "595",
              "596",
              "590",
              "593"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 595."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 316 + 438?",
            "answers": [
              "754",
              "744",
              "764",
              "759"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 754."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 370 + 458?",
            "answers": [
              "828",
              "831",
              "813",
              "830"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 828."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 241 + 381?",
            "answers": [
              "620",
              "622",
              "625",
              "637"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 622."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 70 + 241?",
            "answers": [
              "296",
              "301",
              "316",
              "311"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 311."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 389 + 140?",
            "answers": [
              "534",
              "539",
              "519",
              "529"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 529."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 119 + 309?",
            "answers": [
              "443",
              "418",
              "428",
              "438"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 428."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 500 + 371?",
            "answers": [
              "873",
              "874",
              "871",
              "870"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 871."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 452 + 440?",
            "answers": [
              "891",
              "892",
              "890",
              "902"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 892."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 102 + 423?",
            "answers": [
              "525",
              "528",
              "510",
              "540"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 525."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 121 + 125?",
            "answers": [
              "247",
              "256",
              "246",
              "241"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 246."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 310 + 384?",
            "answers": [
              "697",
              "694",
              "689",
              "696"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 694."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 191 + 229?",
            "answers": [
              "430",
              "423",
              "420",
              "422"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 420."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 432 + 484?",
            "answers": [
              "918",
              "916",
              "917",
              "915"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 916."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 492 + 263?",
            "answers": [
              "770",
              "754",
              "745",
              "755"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 755."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 107 + 69?",
            "answers": [
              "176",
              "175",
              "173",
              "191"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 176."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 390 + 169?",
            "answers": [
              "554",
              "569",
              "544",
              "559"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 559."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 269 + 377?",
            "answers": [
              "656",
              "646",
              "631",
              "645"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 646."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 328 + 209?",
            "answers": [
              "527",
              "547",
              "536",
              "537"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 537."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 335 + 115?",
            "answers": [
              "450",
              "435",
              "453",
              "455"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 450."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 254 + 410?",
            "answers": [
              "661",
              "664",
              "654",
              "666"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 664."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 218 + 407?",
            "answers": [
              "626",
              "627",
              "625",
              "640"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 625."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 233 + 310?",
            "answers": [
              "540",
              "543",
              "544",
              "533"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 543."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 238 + 139?",
            "answers": [
              "377",
              "378",
              "374",
              "367"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 377."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 279 + 415?",
            "answers": [
              "695",
              "684",
              "679",
              "694"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 694."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 242 + 476?",
            "answers": [
              "708",
              "717",
              "718",
              "733"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 718."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 111 + 63?",
            "answers": [
              "177",
              "175",
              "176",
              "174"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 174."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 461 + 196?",
            "answers": [
              "656",
              "672",
              "655",
              "657"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 657."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 234 + 165?",
            "answers": [
              "402",
              "404",
              "384",
              "399"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 399."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 219 + 173?",
            "answers": [
              "395",
              "392",
              "407",
              "394"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 392."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 150 + 287?",
            "answers": [
              "447",
              "437",
              "436",
              "439"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 437."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 273 + 418?",
            "answers": [
              "691",
              "681",
              "689",
              "701"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 691."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 496 + 362?",
            "answers": [
              "863",
              "859",
              "857",
              "858"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 858."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 132 + 406?",
            "answers": [
              "539",
              "538",
              "541",
              "540"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 538."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 447 + 198?",
            "answers": [
              "648",
              "640",
              "645",
              "642"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 645."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 348 + 247?",
            "answers": [
              "594",
              "585",
              "595",
              "598"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 595."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 136 + 226?",
            "answers": [
              "377",
              "357",
              "367",
              "362"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 362."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 129 + 132?",
            "answers": [
              "263",
              "266",
              "261",
              "259"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 261."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 201 + 147?",
            "answers": [
              "353",
              "333",
              "348",
              "346"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 348."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 63 + 142?",
            "answers": [
              "204",
              "200",
              "205",
              "210"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 205."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 101 + 174?",
            "answers": [
              "275",
              "274",
              "260",
              "272"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 275."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 272 + 138?",
            "answers": [
              "413",
              "400",
              "395",
              "410"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 410."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 262 + 129?",
            "answers": [
              "389",
              "401",
              "391",
              "388"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 391."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 347 + 238?",
            "answers": [
              "600",
              "586",
              "585",
              "570"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 585."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 271 + 421?",
            "answers": [
              "697",
              "692",
              "687",
              "689"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 692."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 308 + 124?",
            "answers": [
              "447",
              "437",
              "432",
              "442"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 432."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 168 + 305?",
            "answers": [
              "463",
              "488",
              "471",
              "473"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 473."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 305 + 418?",
            "answers": [
              "720",
              "733",
              "724",
              "723"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 723."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 417 + 494?",
            "answers": [
              "911",
              "914",
              "901",
              "909"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 911."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 127 + 366?",
            "answers": [
              "503",
              "478",
              "493",
              "490"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 493."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 299 + 86?",
            "answers": [
              "380",
              "387",
              "385",
              "384"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 385."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 99 + 439?",
            "answers": [
              "538",
              "540",
              "548",
              "523"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 538."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 115 + 275?",
            "answers": [
              "390",
              "388",
              "405",
              "392"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 390."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 295 + 229?",
            "answers": [
              "521",
              "514",
              "524",
              "523"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 524."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 186 + 343?",
            "answers": [
              "529",
              "519",
              "514",
              "532"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 529."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 279 + 248?",
            "answers": [
              "527",
              "522",
              "537",
              "524"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 527."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 436 + 123?",
            "answers": [
              "569",
              "556",
              "562",
              "559"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 559."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 132 + 182?",
            "answers": [
              "314",
              "313",
              "315",
              "319"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 314."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 411 + 168?",
            "answers": [
              "589",
              "581",
              "576",
              "579"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 579."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 277 + 462?",
            "answers": [
              "739",
              "738",
              "754",
              "744"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 739."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 222 + 282?",
            "answers": [
              "514",
              "501",
              "489",
              "504"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 504."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 461 + 188?",
            "answers": [
              "659",
              "644",
              "649",
              "651"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 649."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 138 + 379?",
            "answers": [
              "517",
              "515",
              "520",
              "518"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 517."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 338 + 264?",
            "answers": [
              "617",
              "612",
              "600",
              "602"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 602."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 168 + 429?",
            "answers": [
              "607",
              "599",
              "597",
              "595"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 597."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 263 + 192?",
            "answers": [
              "458",
              "457",
              "470",
              "455"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 455."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 78 + 172?",
            "answers": [
              "252",
              "245",
              "250",
              "251"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 250."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 70 + 489?",
            "answers": [
              "559",
              "558",
              "554",
              "564"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 559."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 402 + 83?",
            "answers": [
              "485",
              "488",
              "475",
              "487"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 485."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 216 + 459?",
            "answers": [
              "685",
              "676",
              "672",
              "675"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 675."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 389 + 396?",
            "answers": [
              "785",
              "782",
              "795",
              "788"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 785."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 196 + 120?",
            "answers": [
              "319",
              "317",
              "315",
              "316"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 316."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 89 + 240?",
            "answers": [
              "326",
              "329",
              "339",
              "328"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 329."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 487 + 78?",
            "answers": [
              "564",
              "565",
              "550",
              "580"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 565."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 421 + 446?",
            "answers": [
              "867",
              "877",
              "866",
              "882"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 867."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 471 + 443?",
            "answers": [
              "912",
              "915",
              "924",
              "914"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 914."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 153 + 351?",
            "answers": [
              "504",
              "506",
              "503",
              "502"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 504."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 238 + 310?",
            "answers": [
              "548",
              "553",
              "547",
              "543"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 548."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 380 + 118?",
            "answers": [
              "493",
              "499",
              "508",
              "498"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 498."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 251 + 398?",
            "answers": [
              "659",
              "649",
              "646",
              "651"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 649."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 157 + 383?",
            "answers": [
              "545",
              "537",
              "535",
              "540"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 540."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 272 + 120?",
            "answers": [
              "393",
              "392",
              "395",
              "397"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 392."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 52 + 82?",
            "answers": [
              "134",
              "144",
              "149",
              "139"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 134."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 176 + 77?",
            "answers": [
              "253",
              "250",
              "252",
              "255"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 253."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 325 + 209?",
            "answers": [
              "544",
              "535",
              "534",
              "549"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 534."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 139 + 217?",
            "answers": [
              "356",
              "355",
              "359",
              "353"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 356."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 377 + 224?",
            "answers": [
              "603",
              "591",
              "601",
              "616"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 601."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 369 + 405?",
            "answers": [
              "759",
              "775",
              "774",
              "764"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 774."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 117 + 221?",
            "answers": [
              "335",
              "348",
              "336",
              "338"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 338."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 276 + 61?",
            "answers": [
              "337",
              "340",
              "327",
              "322"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 337."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 332 + 120?",
            "answers": [
              "452",
              "467",
              "454",
              "447"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 452."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 108 + 266?",
            "answers": [
              "364",
              "376",
              "374",
              "384"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 374."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 123 + 280?",
            "answers": [
              "406",
              "400",
              "408",
              "403"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 403."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 175 + 134?",
            "answers": [
              "314",
              "309",
              "307",
              "299"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 309."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 170 + 52?",
            "answers": [
              "220",
              "222",
              "232",
              "221"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 222."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 313 + 209?",
            "answers": [
              "507",
              "537",
              "512",
              "522"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 522."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 175 + 238?",
            "answers": [
              "418",
              "415",
              "413",
              "412"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 413."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 298 + 69?",
            "answers": [
              "369",
              "357",
              "352",
              "367"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 367."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 331 + 421?",
            "answers": [
              "751",
              "749",
              "752",
              "762"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 752."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 368 + 495?",
            "answers": [
              "863",
              "873",
              "868",
              "878"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 863."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 492 + 278?",
            "answers": [
              "755",
              "770",
              "768",
              "760"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 770."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 390 + 423?",
            "answers": [
              "813",
              "812",
              "823",
              "815"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 813."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 392 + 120?",
            "answers": [
              "512",
              "510",
              "515",
              "517"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 512."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 136 + 151?",
            "answers": [
              "284",
              "287",
              "297",
              "289"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 287."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 291 + 498?",
            "answers": [
              "786",
              "791",
              "790",
              "789"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 789."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 208 + 215?",
            "answers": [
              "421",
              "423",
              "438",
              "426"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 423."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 274 + 399?",
            "answers": [
              "673",
              "668",
              "675",
              "674"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 673."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 420 + 112?",
            "answers": [
              "532",
              "530",
              "527",
              "529"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 532."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 222 + 120?",
            "answers": [
              "341",
              "343",
              "352",
              "342"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 342."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 497 + 340?",
            "answers": [
              "840",
              "837",
              "852",
              "822"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 837."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 445 + 469?",
            "answers": [
              "912",
              "899",
              "924",
              "914"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 914."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 393 + 327?",
            "answers": [
              "710",
              "717",
              "720",
              "722"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 720."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 312 + 492?",
            "answers": [
              "799",
              "804",
              "802",
              "814"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 804."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 91 + 256?",
            "answers": [
              "346",
              "347",
              "344",
              "348"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 347."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 396 - 307?",
            "answers": [
              "104",
              "74",
              "94",
              "89"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 89."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 275 - 258?",
            "answers": [
              "2",
              "32",
              "15",
              "17"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 17."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 100 - 52?",
            "answers": [
              "43",
              "48",
              "46",
              "47"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 48."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 298 - 245?",
            "answers": [
              "55",
              "38",
              "48",
              "53"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 53."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 282 - 250?",
            "answers": [
              "32",
              "35",
              "22",
              "17"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 32."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 784 - 589?",
            "answers": [
              "190",
              "194",
              "195",
              "198"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 195."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 125 - 82?",
            "answers": [
              "43",
              "40",
              "53",
              "44"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 43."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 648 - 236?",
            "answers": [
              "412",
              "409",
              "407",
              "410"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 412."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 512 - 484?",
            "answers": [
              "33",
              "27",
              "28",
              "23"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 28."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 836 - 339?",
            "answers": [
              "497",
              "492",
              "494",
              "487"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 497."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 177 - 102?",
            "answers": [
              "75",
              "74",
              "85",
              "90"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 75."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 611 - 468?",
            "answers": [
              "158",
              "128",
              "148",
              "143"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 143."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 311 - 245?",
            "answers": [
              "69",
              "56",
              "66",
              "71"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 66."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 769 - 244?",
            "answers": [
              "525",
              "510",
              "528",
              "522"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 525."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 522 - 196?",
            "answers": [
              "341",
              "321",
              "326",
              "336"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 326."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 672 - 316?",
            "answers": [
              "366",
              "357",
              "356",
              "346"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 356."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 516 - 469?",
            "answers": [
              "57",
              "47",
              "52",
              "46"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 47."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 497 - 128?",
            "answers": [
              "369",
              "384",
              "364",
              "359"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 369."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 471 - 155?",
            "answers": [
              "301",
              "317",
              "316",
              "331"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 316."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 327 - 208?",
            "answers": [
              "124",
              "129",
              "119",
              "118"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 119."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 415 - 324?",
            "answers": [
              "86",
              "93",
              "91",
              "94"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 91."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 390 - 249?",
            "answers": [
              "126",
              "151",
              "141",
              "131"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 141."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 365 - 86?",
            "answers": [
              "282",
              "264",
              "276",
              "279"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 279."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 230 - 122?",
            "answers": [
              "108",
              "106",
              "107",
              "111"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 108."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 671 - 244?",
            "answers": [
              "427",
              "429",
              "424",
              "432"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 427."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 273 - 119?",
            "answers": [
              "159",
              "156",
              "155",
              "154"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 154."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 632 - 82?",
            "answers": [
              "552",
              "545",
              "550",
              "547"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 550."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 479 - 215?",
            "answers": [
              "267",
              "269",
              "263",
              "264"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 264."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 434 - 180?",
            "answers": [
              "251",
              "257",
              "254",
              "269"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 254."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 583 - 342?",
            "answers": [
              "256",
              "244",
              "246",
              "241"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 241."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 882 - 678?",
            "answers": [
              "203",
              "219",
              "204",
              "205"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 204."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 974 - 107?",
            "answers": [
              "857",
              "872",
              "867",
              "877"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 867."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 645 - 348?",
            "answers": [
              "299",
              "287",
              "297",
              "295"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 297."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 281 - 176?",
            "answers": [
              "105",
              "104",
              "100",
              "115"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 105."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 745 - 730?",
            "answers": [
              "14",
              "5",
              "12",
              "15"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 15."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 155 - 140?",
            "answers": [
              "15",
              "30",
              "17",
              "10"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 15."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 635 - 213?",
            "answers": [
              "417",
              "407",
              "422",
              "432"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 422."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 897 - 171?",
            "answers": [
              "723",
              "726",
              "711",
              "725"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 726."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 453 - 144?",
            "answers": [
              "308",
              "309",
              "304",
              "294"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 309."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 932 - 329?",
            "answers": [
              "593",
              "603",
              "613",
              "608"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 603."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 459 - 129?",
            "answers": [
              "340",
              "345",
              "330",
              "332"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 330."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 153 - 79?",
            "answers": [
              "84",
              "69",
              "74",
              "64"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 74."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 314 - 314?",
            "answers": [
              "5",
              "11",
              "3",
              "0"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 0."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 898 - 602?",
            "answers": [
              "296",
              "294",
              "286",
              "298"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 296."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 861 - 290?",
            "answers": [
              "561",
              "576",
              "572",
              "571"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 571."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 489 - 217?",
            "answers": [
              "262",
              "271",
              "267",
              "272"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 272."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 577 - 328?",
            "answers": [
              "249",
              "248",
              "252",
              "264"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 249."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 667 - 401?",
            "answers": [
              "267",
              "266",
              "251",
              "261"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 266."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 849 - 511?",
            "answers": [
              "338",
              "337",
              "336",
              "341"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 338."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 444 - 387?",
            "answers": [
              "58",
              "47",
              "57",
              "55"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 57."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 887 - 127?",
            "answers": [
              "760",
              "763",
              "775",
              "757"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 760."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 841 - 88?",
            "answers": [
              "755",
              "753",
              "748",
              "752"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 753."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 147 - 89?",
            "answers": [
              "59",
              "48",
              "61",
              "58"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 58."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 386 - 375?",
            "answers": [
              "6",
              "1",
              "21",
              "11"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 11."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 468 - 219?",
            "answers": [
              "249",
              "246",
              "252",
              "254"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 249."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 317 - 93?",
            "answers": [
              "225",
              "224",
              "222",
              "219"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 224."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 198 - 81?",
            "answers": [
              "117",
              "122",
              "119",
              "114"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 117."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 488 - 383?",
            "answers": [
              "95",
              "105",
              "115",
              "110"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 105."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 396 - 77?",
            "answers": [
              "322",
              "319",
              "304",
              "329"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 319."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 780 - 623?",
            "answers": [
              "156",
              "155",
              "157",
              "172"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 157."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 531 - 369?",
            "answers": [
              "164",
              "162",
              "165",
              "160"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 162."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 403 - 75?",
            "answers": [
              "325",
              "338",
              "328",
              "326"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 328."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 450 - 243?",
            "answers": [
              "207",
              "212",
              "202",
              "206"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 207."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 560 - 320?",
            "answers": [
              "240",
              "238",
              "250",
              "243"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 240."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 869 - 786?",
            "answers": [
              "83",
              "80",
              "86",
              "68"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 83."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 278 - 254?",
            "answers": [
              "9",
              "26",
              "19",
              "24"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 24."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 310 - 164?",
            "answers": [
              "146",
              "141",
              "148",
              "161"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 146."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 648 - 566?",
            "answers": [
              "87",
              "85",
              "82",
              "67"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 82."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 503 - 399?",
            "answers": [
              "106",
              "109",
              "104",
              "101"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 104."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 586 - 428?",
            "answers": [
              "155",
              "173",
              "148",
              "158"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 158."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 444 - 363?",
            "answers": [
              "96",
              "81",
              "91",
              "66"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 81."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 373 - 67?",
            "answers": [
              "321",
              "306",
              "311",
              "308"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 306."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 849 - 68?",
            "answers": [
              "778",
              "780",
              "783",
              "781"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 781."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 964 - 179?",
            "answers": [
              "770",
              "785",
              "786",
              "800"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 785."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 109 - 80?",
            "answers": [
              "31",
              "29",
              "39",
              "44"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 29."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 703 - 424?",
            "answers": [
              "281",
              "279",
              "284",
              "294"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 279."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 832 - 677?",
            "answers": [
              "153",
              "154",
              "158",
              "155"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 155."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 989 - 827?",
            "answers": [
              "159",
              "162",
              "172",
              "163"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 162."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 853 - 239?",
            "answers": [
              "624",
              "604",
              "613",
              "614"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 614."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 966 - 133?",
            "answers": [
              "838",
              "831",
              "833",
              "832"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 833."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 881 - 599?",
            "answers": [
              "282",
              "280",
              "281",
              "267"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 282."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 664 - 412?",
            "answers": [
              "253",
              "252",
              "247",
              "267"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 252."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 777 - 138?",
            "answers": [
              "639",
              "642",
              "637",
              "644"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 639."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 687 - 258?",
            "answers": [
              "427",
              "431",
              "419",
              "429"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 429."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 584 - 382?",
            "answers": [
              "202",
              "192",
              "212",
              "204"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 202."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 760 - 382?",
            "answers": [
              "368",
              "377",
              "375",
              "378"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 378."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 519 - 428?",
            "answers": [
              "91",
              "101",
              "88",
              "89"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 91."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 614 - 322?",
            "answers": [
              "292",
              "290",
              "297",
              "307"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 292."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 187 - 84?",
            "answers": [
              "93",
              "103",
              "105",
              "118"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 103."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 697 - 461?",
            "answers": [
              "226",
              "238",
              "246",
              "236"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 236."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 175 - 59?",
            "answers": [
              "121",
              "113",
              "114",
              "116"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 116."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 661 - 257?",
            "answers": [
              "405",
              "404",
              "409",
              "406"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 404."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 961 - 841?",
            "answers": [
              "119",
              "121",
              "120",
              "135"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 120."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 592 - 348?",
            "answers": [
              "241",
              "259",
              "244",
              "239"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 244."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 631 - 557?",
            "answers": [
              "76",
              "72",
              "74",
              "59"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 74."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 441 - 243?",
            "answers": [
              "203",
              "188",
              "198",
              "196"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 198."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 791 - 757?",
            "answers": [
              "31",
              "24",
              "32",
              "34"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 34."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 249 - 205?",
            "answers": [
              "59",
              "47",
              "29",
              "44"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 44."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 747 - 138?",
            "answers": [
              "599",
              "611",
              "609",
              "608"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 609."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 277 - 69?",
            "answers": [
              "223",
              "205",
              "198",
              "208"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 208."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 860 - 224?",
            "answers": [
              "636",
              "651",
              "621",
              "634"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 636."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 173 - 87?",
            "answers": [
              "88",
              "83",
              "86",
              "76"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 86."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 574 - 496?",
            "answers": [
              "68",
              "78",
              "76",
              "75"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 78."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 391 - 88?",
            "answers": [
              "288",
              "298",
              "313",
              "303"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 303."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 947 - 203?",
            "answers": [
              "744",
              "745",
              "742",
              "743"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 744."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 699 - 260?",
            "answers": [
              "441",
              "437",
              "434",
              "439"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 439."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 159 - 100?",
            "answers": [
              "64",
              "69",
              "58",
              "59"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 59."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 907 - 571?",
            "answers": [
              "331",
              "333",
              "336",
              "326"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 336."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 646 - 304?",
            "answers": [
              "344",
              "341",
              "342",
              "337"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 342."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 369 - 304?",
            "answers": [
              "63",
              "65",
              "67",
              "62"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 65."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 373 - 365?",
            "answers": [
              "13",
              "8",
              "3",
              "18"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 8."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 150 - 124?",
            "answers": [
              "21",
              "26",
              "41",
              "23"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 26."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 112 - 86?",
            "answers": [
              "29",
              "26",
              "41",
              "28"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 26."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 657 - 100?",
            "answers": [
              "572",
              "554",
              "556",
              "557"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 557."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 522 - 181?",
            "answers": [
              "341",
              "339",
              "351",
              "340"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 341."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 691 - 334?",
            "answers": [
              "372",
              "352",
              "357",
              "362"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 357."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 212 - 158?",
            "answers": [
              "57",
              "54",
              "56",
              "69"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 54."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 676 - 283?",
            "answers": [
              "393",
              "395",
              "403",
              "408"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 393."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 989 - 746?",
            "answers": [
              "240",
              "243",
              "248",
              "253"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 243."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 129 - 69?",
            "answers": [
              "62",
              "50",
              "70",
              "60"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 60."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 521 - 414?",
            "answers": [
              "108",
              "117",
              "104",
              "107"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 107."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 750 - 156?",
            "answers": [
              "579",
              "594",
              "597",
              "593"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 594."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 985 - 309?",
            "answers": [
              "691",
              "661",
              "676",
              "681"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 676."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 756 - 229?",
            "answers": [
              "528",
              "542",
              "527",
              "537"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 527."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 724 - 240?",
            "answers": [
              "483",
              "484",
              "487",
              "469"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 484."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 911 - 61?",
            "answers": [
              "860",
              "845",
              "850",
              "849"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 850."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 983 - 898?",
            "answers": [
              "83",
              "80",
              "75",
              "85"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 85."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 707 - 191?",
            "answers": [
              "531",
              "513",
              "516",
              "521"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 516."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 842 - 630?",
            "answers": [
              "197",
              "212",
              "211",
              "227"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 212."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 878 - 59?",
            "answers": [
              "820",
              "829",
              "816",
              "819"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 819."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 555 - 193?",
            "answers": [
              "360",
              "362",
              "367",
              "357"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 362."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 777 - 215?",
            "answers": [
              "567",
              "562",
              "559",
              "560"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 562."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 196 - 102?",
            "answers": [
              "96",
              "84",
              "79",
              "94"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 94."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 541 - 148?",
            "answers": [
              "388",
              "396",
              "393",
              "378"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 393."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 839 - 211?",
            "answers": [
              "631",
              "638",
              "628",
              "613"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 628."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 233 - 199?",
            "answers": [
              "31",
              "34",
              "39",
              "33"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 34."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 151 - 54?",
            "answers": [
              "94",
              "97",
              "99",
              "112"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 97."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 128 - 69?",
            "answers": [
              "56",
              "59",
              "57",
              "54"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 59."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 318 - 99?",
            "answers": [
              "234",
              "219",
              "221",
              "204"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 219."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 210 - 61?",
            "answers": [
              "164",
              "149",
              "147",
              "152"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 149."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 339 - 175?",
            "answers": [
              "169",
              "164",
              "159",
              "154"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 164."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 455 - 89?",
            "answers": [
              "356",
              "365",
              "371",
              "366"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 366."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 394 - 213?",
            "answers": [
              "181",
              "176",
              "186",
              "171"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 181."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 540 - 320?",
            "answers": [
              "222",
              "210",
              "205",
              "220"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 220."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 657 - 456?",
            "answers": [
              "186",
              "203",
              "201",
              "191"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 201."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 226 - 153?",
            "answers": [
              "73",
              "76",
              "88",
              "58"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 73."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 617 - 224?",
            "answers": [
              "388",
              "393",
              "408",
              "398"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 393."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 314 - 118?",
            "answers": [
              "193",
              "196",
              "206",
              "195"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 196."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 701 - 635?",
            "answers": [
              "61",
              "51",
              "81",
              "66"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 66."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 318 - 127?",
            "answers": [
              "191",
              "176",
              "181",
              "193"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 191."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 518 - 161?",
            "answers": [
              "357",
              "362",
              "354",
              "359"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 357."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 149 - 53?",
            "answers": [
              "111",
              "86",
              "96",
              "95"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 96."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 855 - 850?",
            "answers": [
              "6",
              "20",
              "5",
              "0"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 5."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 295 - 290?",
            "answers": [
              "8",
              "5",
              "0",
              "7"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 5."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 858 - 658?",
            "answers": [
              "200",
              "203",
              "190",
              "185"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 200."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 926 - 365?",
            "answers": [
              "561",
              "556",
              "562",
              "560"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 561."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 419 - 376?",
            "answers": [
              "42",
              "43",
              "41",
              "53"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 43."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 138 - 122?",
            "answers": [
              "16",
              "1",
              "26",
              "6"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 16."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 185 - 85?",
            "answers": [
              "103",
              "90",
              "100",
              "95"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 100."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 391 - 160?",
            "answers": [
              "231",
              "233",
              "228",
              "246"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 231."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 789 - 519?",
            "answers": [
              "260",
              "272",
              "270",
              "267"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 270."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 736 - 632?",
            "answers": [
              "102",
              "114",
              "104",
              "99"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 104."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 384 - 264?",
            "answers": [
              "118",
              "125",
              "120",
              "110"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 120."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 584 - 483?",
            "answers": [
              "111",
              "101",
              "91",
              "104"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 101."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 989 - 443?",
            "answers": [
              "546",
              "551",
              "547",
              "548"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 546."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 945 - 462?",
            "answers": [
              "486",
              "478",
              "480",
              "483"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 483."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 163 - 90?",
            "answers": [
              "73",
              "74",
              "58",
              "70"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 73."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 982 - 422?",
            "answers": [
              "561",
              "575",
              "560",
              "558"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 560."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 252 - 242?",
            "answers": [
              "12",
              "5",
              "15",
              "10"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 10."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 949 - 894?",
            "answers": [
              "58",
              "55",
              "56",
              "53"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 55."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 829 - 292?",
            "answers": [
              "542",
              "552",
              "537",
              "540"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 537."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 912 - 912?",
            "answers": [
              "3",
              "0",
              "1",
              "5"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 0."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 147 - 130?",
            "answers": [
              "32",
              "17",
              "16",
              "14"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 17."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 131 - 85?",
            "answers": [
              "47",
              "46",
              "36",
              "41"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 46."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 206 - 82?",
            "answers": [
              "124",
              "134",
              "122",
              "126"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 124."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 571 - 368?",
            "answers": [
              "213",
              "203",
              "205",
              "208"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 203."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 781 - 697?",
            "answers": [
              "69",
              "74",
              "81",
              "84"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 84."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 510 - 164?",
            "answers": [
              "343",
              "347",
              "346",
              "336"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 346."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 213 - 159?",
            "answers": [
              "54",
              "51",
              "56",
              "64"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 54."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 258 - 205?",
            "answers": [
              "53",
              "54",
              "38",
              "43"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 53."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 138 - 64?",
            "answers": [
              "84",
              "69",
              "72",
              "74"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 74."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 655 - 356?",
            "answers": [
              "297",
              "302",
              "284",
              "299"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 299."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 999 - 943?",
            "answers": [
              "53",
              "61",
              "56",
              "54"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 56."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 650 - 367?",
            "answers": [
              "286",
              "283",
              "293",
              "273"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 283."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 356 - 248?",
            "answers": [
              "93",
              "123",
              "108",
              "98"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 108."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 543 - 415?",
            "answers": [
              "138",
              "123",
              "128",
              "118"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 128."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 121 - 56?",
            "answers": [
              "55",
              "67",
              "65",
              "63"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 65."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 119 - 110?",
            "answers": [
              "10",
              "9",
              "19",
              "11"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 9."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 775 - 249?",
            "answers": [
              "527",
              "541",
              "516",
              "526"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 526."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 432 - 419?",
            "answers": [
              "10",
              "12",
              "13",
              "11"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 13."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 972 - 190?",
            "answers": [
              "767",
              "772",
              "782",
              "783"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 782."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 658 - 150?",
            "answers": [
              "509",
              "508",
              "493",
              "503"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 508."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 216 - 106?",
            "answers": [
              "125",
              "110",
              "100",
              "95"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 110."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 345 - 185?",
            "answers": [
              "158",
              "160",
              "161",
              "170"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 160."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 640 - 459?",
            "answers": [
              "181",
              "182",
              "196",
              "183"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 181."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 497 - 138?",
            "answers": [
              "357",
              "369",
              "344",
              "359"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 359."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 812 - 325?",
            "answers": [
              "487",
              "492",
              "472",
              "497"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 487."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 754 - 155?",
            "answers": [
              "599",
              "596",
              "601",
              "598"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 599."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 945 - 891?",
            "answers": [
              "54",
              "55",
              "51",
              "59"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 54."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 355 - 140?",
            "answers": [
              "200",
              "212",
              "215",
              "225"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 215."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 48 \u00d7 23?",
            "answers": [
              "1104",
              "1094",
              "1106",
              "1114"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1104."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 45 \u00d7 13?",
            "answers": [
              "585",
              "584",
              "570",
              "587"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 585."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 28 \u00d7 19?",
            "answers": [
              "527",
              "532",
              "531",
              "537"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 532."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 39 \u00d7 30?",
            "answers": [
              "1170",
              "1155",
              "1172",
              "1168"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1170."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 22 \u00d7 29?",
            "answers": [
              "633",
              "638",
              "636",
              "653"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 638."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 19 \u00d7 22?",
            "answers": [
              "433",
              "417",
              "403",
              "418"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 418."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 19 \u00d7 30?",
            "answers": [
              "569",
              "570",
              "571",
              "555"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 570."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 27 \u00d7 20?",
            "answers": [
              "540",
              "530",
              "535",
              "550"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 540."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 18 \u00d7 30?",
            "answers": [
              "550",
              "530",
              "539",
              "540"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 540."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 21 \u00d7 6?",
            "answers": [
              "127",
              "126",
              "116",
              "125"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 126."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 33 \u00d7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "459",
              "452",
              "462",
              "457"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 462."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 34 \u00d7 7?",
            "answers": [
              "248",
              "238",
              "253",
              "240"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 238."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 15 \u00d7 23?",
            "answers": [
              "330",
              "346",
              "345",
              "343"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 345."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 22 \u00d7 29?",
            "answers": [
              "643",
              "653",
              "638",
              "636"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 638."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 14 \u00d7 10?",
            "answers": [
              "140",
              "137",
              "145",
              "142"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 140."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 30 \u00d7 17?",
            "answers": [
              "510",
              "508",
              "520",
              "525"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 510."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 36 \u00d7 7?",
            "answers": [
              "254",
              "250",
              "242",
              "252"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 252."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 21 \u00d7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "292",
              "279",
              "294",
              "295"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 294."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 43 \u00d7 27?",
            "answers": [
              "1151",
              "1164",
              "1161",
              "1156"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1161."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 17 \u00d7 28?",
            "answers": [
              "476",
              "481",
              "477",
              "491"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 476."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 17 \u00d7 6?",
            "answers": [
              "102",
              "97",
              "103",
              "107"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 102."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 34 \u00d7 19?",
            "answers": [
              "647",
              "646",
              "636",
              "656"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 646."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 48 \u00d7 19?",
            "answers": [
              "912",
              "910",
              "927",
              "914"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 912."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 22?",
            "answers": [
              "205",
              "223",
              "220",
              "235"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 220."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 30?",
            "answers": [
              "333",
              "335",
              "330",
              "340"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 330."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 46 \u00d7 24?",
            "answers": [
              "1109",
              "1107",
              "1104",
              "1103"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1104."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 41 \u00d7 18?",
            "answers": [
              "741",
              "723",
              "738",
              "740"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 738."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 14 \u00d7 22?",
            "answers": [
              "308",
              "293",
              "310",
              "307"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 308."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 22 \u00d7 20?",
            "answers": [
              "439",
              "425",
              "440",
              "442"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 440."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 23 \u00d7 17?",
            "answers": [
              "401",
              "396",
              "391",
              "393"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 391."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 42 \u00d7 30?",
            "answers": [
              "1275",
              "1260",
              "1261",
              "1259"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1260."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 47 \u00d7 15?",
            "answers": [
              "703",
              "705",
              "700",
              "702"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 705."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 40 \u00d7 6?",
            "answers": [
              "245",
              "240",
              "239",
              "255"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 240."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 48 \u00d7 29?",
            "answers": [
              "1393",
              "1394",
              "1392",
              "1377"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1392."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "154",
              "155",
              "151",
              "144"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 154."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 23 \u00d7 15?",
            "answers": [
              "335",
              "348",
              "355",
              "345"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 345."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 23 \u00d7 15?",
            "answers": [
              "346",
              "348",
              "347",
              "345"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 345."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 33 \u00d7 26?",
            "answers": [
              "868",
              "861",
              "863",
              "858"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 858."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 38 \u00d7 11?",
            "answers": [
              "413",
              "421",
              "418",
              "423"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 418."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 46 \u00d7 13?",
            "answers": [
              "583",
              "595",
              "593",
              "598"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 598."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 26 \u00d7 6?",
            "answers": [
              "141",
              "153",
              "156",
              "159"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 156."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 16 \u00d7 29?",
            "answers": [
              "464",
              "465",
              "474",
              "449"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 464."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 14 \u00d7 8?",
            "answers": [
              "109",
              "112",
              "111",
              "102"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 112."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 45 \u00d7 12?",
            "answers": [
              "538",
              "530",
              "540",
              "537"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 540."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 44 \u00d7 20?",
            "answers": [
              "881",
              "870",
              "885",
              "880"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 880."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 44 \u00d7 5?",
            "answers": [
              "215",
              "220",
              "222",
              "235"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 220."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 25 \u00d7 19?",
            "answers": [
              "475",
              "465",
              "490",
              "485"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 475."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 18 \u00d7 17?",
            "answers": [
              "305",
              "306",
              "316",
              "291"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 306."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 26 \u00d7 8?",
            "answers": [
              "213",
              "208",
              "211",
              "198"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 208."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 40 \u00d7 24?",
            "answers": [
              "960",
              "950",
              "945",
              "963"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 960."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 41 \u00d7 18?",
            "answers": [
              "735",
              "740",
              "738",
              "733"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 738."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 16 \u00d7 10?",
            "answers": [
              "160",
              "158",
              "157",
              "155"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 160."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 23 \u00d7 18?",
            "answers": [
              "404",
              "414",
              "411",
              "412"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 414."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 44 \u00d7 10?",
            "answers": [
              "450",
              "425",
              "440",
              "445"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 440."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 42 \u00d7 15?",
            "answers": [
              "628",
              "645",
              "640",
              "630"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 630."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 39 \u00d7 28?",
            "answers": [
              "1092",
              "1090",
              "1087",
              "1093"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1092."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 34 \u00d7 28?",
            "answers": [
              "967",
              "954",
              "957",
              "952"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 952."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "183",
              "168",
              "163",
              "170"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 168."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 18 \u00d7 15?",
            "answers": [
              "270",
              "275",
              "265",
              "260"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 270."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 19 \u00d7 28?",
            "answers": [
              "522",
              "531",
              "532",
              "542"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 532."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 30 \u00d7 7?",
            "answers": [
              "209",
              "210",
              "195",
              "205"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 210."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 48 \u00d7 24?",
            "answers": [
              "1154",
              "1137",
              "1152",
              "1142"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1152."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 30 \u00d7 18?",
            "answers": [
              "545",
              "540",
              "525",
              "543"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 540."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 49 \u00d7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "686",
              "689",
              "685",
              "701"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 686."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 45 \u00d7 15?",
            "answers": [
              "673",
              "675",
              "680",
              "685"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 675."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 16 \u00d7 21?",
            "answers": [
              "335",
              "336",
              "339",
              "334"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 336."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 40 \u00d7 22?",
            "answers": [
              "880",
              "882",
              "879",
              "865"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 880."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 34 \u00d7 8?",
            "answers": [
              "274",
              "272",
              "262",
              "277"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 272."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 22 \u00d7 29?",
            "answers": [
              "638",
              "640",
              "641",
              "639"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 638."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 44 \u00d7 21?",
            "answers": [
              "929",
              "924",
              "914",
              "919"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 924."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 38 \u00d7 27?",
            "answers": [
              "1028",
              "1027",
              "1029",
              "1026"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1026."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 45 \u00d7 22?",
            "answers": [
              "992",
              "989",
              "987",
              "990"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 990."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 39 \u00d7 30?",
            "answers": [
              "1170",
              "1155",
              "1185",
              "1169"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1170."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 29 \u00d7 17?",
            "answers": [
              "493",
              "494",
              "496",
              "503"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 493."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 46 \u00d7 15?",
            "answers": [
              "690",
              "675",
              "695",
              "691"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 690."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 49 \u00d7 13?",
            "answers": [
              "647",
              "637",
              "634",
              "635"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 637."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 18 \u00d7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "267",
              "252",
              "249",
              "242"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 252."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 27 \u00d7 24?",
            "answers": [
              "663",
              "646",
              "648",
              "643"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 648."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 34 \u00d7 18?",
            "answers": [
              "609",
              "627",
              "612",
              "602"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 612."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 47 \u00d7 25?",
            "answers": [
              "1160",
              "1165",
              "1190",
              "1175"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1175."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 36 \u00d7 25?",
            "answers": [
              "900",
              "885",
              "895",
              "890"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 900."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 47 \u00d7 24?",
            "answers": [
              "1130",
              "1128",
              "1143",
              "1133"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1128."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 18 \u00d7 29?",
            "answers": [
              "517",
              "520",
              "522",
              "512"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 522."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 21 \u00d7 28?",
            "answers": [
              "578",
              "591",
              "588",
              "587"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 588."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 20 \u00d7 22?",
            "answers": [
              "439",
              "450",
              "435",
              "440"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 440."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 50 \u00d7 15?",
            "answers": [
              "751",
              "750",
              "745",
              "755"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 750."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 38 \u00d7 27?",
            "answers": [
              "1021",
              "1027",
              "1026",
              "1025"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1026."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 16 \u00d7 26?",
            "answers": [
              "416",
              "401",
              "411",
              "413"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 416."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 25 \u00d7 18?",
            "answers": [
              "465",
              "451",
              "450",
              "447"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 450."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 37 \u00d7 27?",
            "answers": [
              "998",
              "996",
              "999",
              "994"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 999."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 14 \u00d7 29?",
            "answers": [
              "406",
              "391",
              "407",
              "405"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 406."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 36 \u00d7 30?",
            "answers": [
              "1077",
              "1083",
              "1085",
              "1080"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1080."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 27 \u00d7 25?",
            "answers": [
              "665",
              "674",
              "660",
              "675"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 675."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 46 \u00d7 12?",
            "answers": [
              "552",
              "557",
              "537",
              "547"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 552."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 16 \u00d7 21?",
            "answers": [
              "336",
              "321",
              "333",
              "335"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 336."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 30 \u00d7 29?",
            "answers": [
              "872",
              "873",
              "860",
              "870"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 870."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 44 \u00d7 26?",
            "answers": [
              "1129",
              "1159",
              "1141",
              "1144"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1144."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 19 \u00d7 8?",
            "answers": [
              "150",
              "153",
              "152",
              "142"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 152."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 50 \u00d7 30?",
            "answers": [
              "1500",
              "1499",
              "1510",
              "1498"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1500."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 22 \u00d7 10?",
            "answers": [
              "219",
              "221",
              "220",
              "223"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 220."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 42 \u00d7 30?",
            "answers": [
              "1259",
              "1260",
              "1261",
              "1262"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1260."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 28 \u00d7 21?",
            "answers": [
              "588",
              "586",
              "591",
              "587"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 588."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 9?",
            "answers": [
              "96",
              "99",
              "102",
              "101"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 99."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 18 \u00d7 18?",
            "answers": [
              "334",
              "324",
              "323",
              "314"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 324."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 34 \u00d7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "474",
              "476",
              "461",
              "477"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 476."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 26 \u00d7 29?",
            "answers": [
              "769",
              "751",
              "754",
              "764"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 754."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 32 \u00d7 15?",
            "answers": [
              "475",
              "470",
              "485",
              "480"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 480."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 29?",
            "answers": [
              "348",
              "363",
              "353",
              "338"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 348."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 28 \u00d7 20?",
            "answers": [
              "550",
              "545",
              "575",
              "560"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 560."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 18 \u00d7 19?",
            "answers": [
              "337",
              "342",
              "343",
              "352"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 342."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 22?",
            "answers": [
              "222",
              "220",
              "219",
              "218"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 220."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 31 \u00d7 15?",
            "answers": [
              "465",
              "468",
              "467",
              "475"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 465."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 50 \u00d7 26?",
            "answers": [
              "1310",
              "1315",
              "1300",
              "1290"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1300."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 45 \u00d7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "630",
              "615",
              "625",
              "632"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 630."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 45 \u00d7 17?",
            "answers": [
              "755",
              "780",
              "768",
              "765"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 765."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 18 \u00d7 24?",
            "answers": [
              "435",
              "430",
              "432",
              "447"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 432."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 46 \u00d7 24?",
            "answers": [
              "1104",
              "1089",
              "1105",
              "1107"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1104."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 47 \u00d7 29?",
            "answers": [
              "1378",
              "1368",
              "1363",
              "1365"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1363."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 43 \u00d7 23?",
            "answers": [
              "987",
              "974",
              "989",
              "984"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 989."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 42 \u00d7 18?",
            "answers": [
              "757",
              "756",
              "753",
              "754"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 756."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 25 \u00d7 19?",
            "answers": [
              "480",
              "475",
              "473",
              "476"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 475."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 34 \u00d7 6?",
            "answers": [
              "201",
              "203",
              "207",
              "204"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 204."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 21 \u00d7 11?",
            "answers": [
              "229",
              "231",
              "246",
              "228"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 231."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 38 \u00d7 29?",
            "answers": [
              "1101",
              "1102",
              "1087",
              "1097"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1102."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 25 \u00d7 22?",
            "answers": [
              "550",
              "552",
              "548",
              "549"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 550."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 30 \u00d7 6?",
            "answers": [
              "175",
              "170",
              "182",
              "180"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 180."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 37 \u00d7 18?",
            "answers": [
              "681",
              "664",
              "666",
              "665"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 666."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 6?",
            "answers": [
              "59",
              "55",
              "61",
              "60"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 60."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 14 \u00d7 18?",
            "answers": [
              "250",
              "253",
              "252",
              "242"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 252."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 20 \u00d7 6?",
            "answers": [
              "121",
              "130",
              "120",
              "123"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 120."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 24 \u00d7 19?",
            "answers": [
              "456",
              "454",
              "458",
              "441"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 456."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 33 \u00d7 15?",
            "answers": [
              "497",
              "490",
              "495",
              "498"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 495."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 25 \u00d7 19?",
            "answers": [
              "475",
              "470",
              "474",
              "460"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 475."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 27 \u00d7 21?",
            "answers": [
              "567",
              "565",
              "557",
              "566"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 567."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 16 \u00d7 29?",
            "answers": [
              "463",
              "459",
              "461",
              "464"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 464."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 14 \u00d7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "186",
              "197",
              "194",
              "196"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 196."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 13 \u00d7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "172",
              "179",
              "184",
              "182"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 182."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 27 \u00d7 19?",
            "answers": [
              "513",
              "523",
              "511",
              "528"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 513."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 20 \u00d7 7?",
            "answers": [
              "142",
              "140",
              "143",
              "139"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 140."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 24 \u00d7 13?",
            "answers": [
              "297",
              "312",
              "317",
              "313"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 312."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 26 \u00d7 11?",
            "answers": [
              "276",
              "286",
              "296",
              "281"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 286."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 26 \u00d7 16?",
            "answers": [
              "415",
              "416",
              "413",
              "421"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 416."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 17?",
            "answers": [
              "170",
              "173",
              "169",
              "155"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 170."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 29 \u00d7 26?",
            "answers": [
              "751",
              "753",
              "764",
              "754"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 754."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 13 \u00d7 17?",
            "answers": [
              "231",
              "221",
              "223",
              "206"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 221."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 17 \u00d7 20?",
            "answers": [
              "340",
              "341",
              "337",
              "345"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 340."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 17 \u00d7 8?",
            "answers": [
              "135",
              "136",
              "134",
              "126"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 136."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 41 \u00d7 7?",
            "answers": [
              "272",
              "287",
              "282",
              "277"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 287."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 30 \u00d7 7?",
            "answers": [
              "210",
              "215",
              "211",
              "220"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 210."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 19 \u00d7 27?",
            "answers": [
              "513",
              "498",
              "523",
              "510"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 513."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 26 \u00d7 13?",
            "answers": [
              "339",
              "335",
              "338",
              "328"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 338."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 24 \u00d7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "341",
              "336",
              "326",
              "338"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 336."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 16 \u00d7 5?",
            "answers": [
              "75",
              "83",
              "95",
              "80"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 80."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 17?",
            "answers": [
              "188",
              "182",
              "187",
              "184"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 187."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 20 \u00d7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "270",
              "280",
              "282",
              "265"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 280."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 7?",
            "answers": [
              "89",
              "84",
              "74",
              "94"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 84."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 22 \u00d7 19?",
            "answers": [
              "417",
              "423",
              "413",
              "418"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 418."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 30 \u00d7 26?",
            "answers": [
              "775",
              "790",
              "795",
              "780"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 780."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 39 \u00d7 29?",
            "answers": [
              "1126",
              "1130",
              "1121",
              "1131"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1131."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 50 \u00d7 20?",
            "answers": [
              "998",
              "1001",
              "1000",
              "985"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1000."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 35 \u00d7 16?",
            "answers": [
              "565",
              "560",
              "575",
              "557"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 560."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 46 \u00d7 16?",
            "answers": [
              "735",
              "736",
              "734",
              "731"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 736."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 29 \u00d7 30?",
            "answers": [
              "880",
              "871",
              "885",
              "870"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 870."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 19 \u00d7 19?",
            "answers": [
              "362",
              "361",
              "356",
              "360"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 361."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 27 \u00d7 22?",
            "answers": [
              "594",
              "597",
              "599",
              "589"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 594."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 11?",
            "answers": [
              "110",
              "125",
              "105",
              "112"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 110."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 30 \u00d7 17?",
            "answers": [
              "510",
              "515",
              "511",
              "500"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 510."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 32 \u00d7 7?",
            "answers": [
              "239",
              "224",
              "219",
              "234"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 224."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 43 \u00d7 6?",
            "answers": [
              "256",
              "255",
              "258",
              "260"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 258."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 30 \u00d7 15?",
            "answers": [
              "465",
              "452",
              "449",
              "450"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 450."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 26 \u00d7 19?",
            "answers": [
              "504",
              "496",
              "491",
              "494"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 494."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 47 \u00d7 8?",
            "answers": [
              "377",
              "366",
              "374",
              "376"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 376."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 35 \u00d7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "492",
              "489",
              "495",
              "490"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 490."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 41 \u00d7 5?",
            "answers": [
              "202",
              "220",
              "205",
              "210"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 205."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 20 \u00d7 26?",
            "answers": [
              "520",
              "517",
              "522",
              "518"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 520."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 37 \u00d7 9?",
            "answers": [
              "331",
              "330",
              "332",
              "333"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 333."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 19 \u00d7 24?",
            "answers": [
              "456",
              "455",
              "471",
              "461"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 456."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 46 \u00d7 12?",
            "answers": [
              "552",
              "553",
              "550",
              "555"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 552."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 50 \u00d7 27?",
            "answers": [
              "1350",
              "1352",
              "1347",
              "1355"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1350."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 29 \u00d7 25?",
            "answers": [
              "740",
              "710",
              "728",
              "725"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 725."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 20 \u00d7 26?",
            "answers": [
              "505",
              "525",
              "517",
              "520"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 520."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 47 \u00d7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "659",
              "658",
              "643",
              "663"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 658."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 44 \u00d7 23?",
            "answers": [
              "1009",
              "1013",
              "1012",
              "1007"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1012."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 24 \u00d7 20?",
            "answers": [
              "480",
              "485",
              "483",
              "479"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 480."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 15 \u00d7 15?",
            "answers": [
              "227",
              "225",
              "235",
              "210"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 225."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 31 \u00d7 20?",
            "answers": [
              "605",
              "615",
              "610",
              "620"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 620."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 7?",
            "answers": [
              "69",
              "82",
              "84",
              "86"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 84."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 8?",
            "answers": [
              "91",
              "95",
              "96",
              "106"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 96."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 22 \u00d7 22?",
            "answers": [
              "484",
              "489",
              "482",
              "486"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 484."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 16 \u00d7 17?",
            "answers": [
              "273",
              "287",
              "272",
              "271"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 272."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 21 \u00d7 8?",
            "answers": [
              "170",
              "168",
              "178",
              "165"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 168."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 50 \u00d7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "700",
              "701",
              "703",
              "702"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 700."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 26 \u00d7 21?",
            "answers": [
              "556",
              "561",
              "547",
              "546"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 546."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 25 \u00d7 11?",
            "answers": [
              "285",
              "270",
              "277",
              "275"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 275."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 39 \u00d7 27?",
            "answers": [
              "1051",
              "1053",
              "1056",
              "1050"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1053."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 47 \u00d7 16?",
            "answers": [
              "749",
              "742",
              "752",
              "757"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 752."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 27 \u00d7 26?",
            "answers": [
              "707",
              "705",
              "702",
              "697"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 702."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 13 \u00d7 22?",
            "answers": [
              "288",
              "276",
              "287",
              "286"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 286."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 29 \u00d7 27?",
            "answers": [
              "785",
              "783",
              "768",
              "793"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 783."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 46 \u00d7 13?",
            "answers": [
              "603",
              "613",
              "595",
              "598"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 598."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 18 \u00d7 21?",
            "answers": [
              "378",
              "368",
              "373",
              "388"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 378."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 38 \u00d7 5?",
            "answers": [
              "190",
              "192",
              "175",
              "205"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 190."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 33 \u00d7 10?",
            "answers": [
              "345",
              "328",
              "332",
              "330"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 330."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 31 \u00d7 17?",
            "answers": [
              "512",
              "537",
              "528",
              "527"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 527."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 31 \u00d7 9?",
            "answers": [
              "279",
              "284",
              "280",
              "294"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 279."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 23 \u00d7 27?",
            "answers": [
              "621",
              "619",
              "624",
              "626"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 621."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 27 \u00d7 17?",
            "answers": [
              "469",
              "459",
              "444",
              "462"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 459."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 13 \u00d7 23?",
            "answers": [
              "299",
              "296",
              "302",
              "298"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 299."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 46 \u00d7 16?",
            "answers": [
              "738",
              "737",
              "736",
              "731"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 736."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 50 \u00d7 20?",
            "answers": [
              "1005",
              "1000",
              "998",
              "999"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1000."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 17 \u00d7 30?",
            "answers": [
              "510",
              "525",
              "505",
              "500"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 510."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 48 \u00d7 17?",
            "answers": [
              "801",
              "814",
              "813",
              "816"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 816."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 20 \u00d7 7?",
            "answers": [
              "130",
              "140",
              "139",
              "143"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 140."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 18 \u00d7 25?",
            "answers": [
              "455",
              "450",
              "460",
              "449"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 450."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "140",
              "143",
              "130",
              "139"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 140."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 47 \u00d7 30?",
            "answers": [
              "1410",
              "1412",
              "1411",
              "1425"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1410."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 21 \u00d7 29?",
            "answers": [
              "612",
              "594",
              "608",
              "609"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 609."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 19 \u00d7 11?",
            "answers": [
              "211",
              "209",
              "207",
              "199"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 209."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 43 \u00d7 24?",
            "answers": [
              "1017",
              "1034",
              "1032",
              "1030"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1032."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 32 \u00d7 22?",
            "answers": [
              "706",
              "704",
              "701",
              "689"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 704."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 20 \u00d7 24?",
            "answers": [
              "481",
              "480",
              "465",
              "478"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 480."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 6?",
            "answers": [
              "71",
              "66",
              "81",
              "64"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 66."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 40 \u00d7 15?",
            "answers": [
              "599",
              "600",
              "610",
              "585"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 600."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 44 \u00d7 26?",
            "answers": [
              "1149",
              "1139",
              "1144",
              "1142"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1144."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 28 \u00d7 28?",
            "answers": [
              "781",
              "785",
              "774",
              "784"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 784."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 29 \u00d7 20?",
            "answers": [
              "579",
              "577",
              "580",
              "575"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 580."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 22 \u00d7 26?",
            "answers": [
              "572",
              "574",
              "569",
              "582"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 572."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 32 \u00d7 8?",
            "answers": [
              "261",
              "271",
              "251",
              "256"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 256."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 46 \u00d7 15?",
            "answers": [
              "689",
              "687",
              "692",
              "690"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 690."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 25?",
            "answers": [
              "250",
              "248",
              "240",
              "260"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 250."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 36 \u00d7 10?",
            "answers": [
              "370",
              "361",
              "365",
              "360"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 360."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 22 \u00d7 27?",
            "answers": [
              "593",
              "597",
              "589",
              "594"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 594."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 48 \u00d7 6?",
            "answers": [
              "285",
              "288",
              "291",
              "278"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 288."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 14 \u00d7 11?",
            "answers": [
              "154",
              "139",
              "151",
              "157"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 154."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 19 \u00d7 16?",
            "answers": [
              "304",
              "305",
              "289",
              "319"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 304."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 14 \u00d7 10?",
            "answers": [
              "142",
              "141",
              "140",
              "145"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 140."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 17 \u00d7 19?",
            "answers": [
              "328",
              "323",
              "325",
              "326"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 323."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 50 \u00d7 18?",
            "answers": [
              "903",
              "905",
              "895",
              "900"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 900."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 23 \u00d7 27?",
            "answers": [
              "611",
              "616",
              "621",
              "622"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 621."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 44 \u00d7 15?",
            "answers": [
              "675",
              "660",
              "650",
              "662"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 660."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 21 \u00d7 5?",
            "answers": [
              "107",
              "105",
              "100",
              "103"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 105."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 48 \u00d7 24?",
            "answers": [
              "1167",
              "1149",
              "1152",
              "1162"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1152."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 46 \u00d7 7?",
            "answers": [
              "321",
              "322",
              "332",
              "317"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 322."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 19 \u00d7 26?",
            "answers": [
              "494",
              "493",
              "509",
              "484"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 494."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 32 \u00d7 24?",
            "answers": [
              "758",
              "769",
              "773",
              "768"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 768."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 44 \u00d7 22?",
            "answers": [
              "967",
              "958",
              "969",
              "968"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 968."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 41 \u00d7 20?",
            "answers": [
              "820",
              "835",
              "821",
              "810"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 820."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 5?",
            "answers": [
              "70",
              "54",
              "55",
              "60"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 55."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 41 \u00d7 5?",
            "answers": [
              "203",
              "190",
              "220",
              "205"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 205."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 42 \u00d7 8?",
            "answers": [
              "336",
              "339",
              "321",
              "341"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 336."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 40 \u00d7 26?",
            "answers": [
              "1039",
              "1040",
              "1042",
              "1045"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1040."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 42 \u00d7 30?",
            "answers": [
              "1262",
              "1258",
              "1265",
              "1260"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1260."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 42 \u00d7 7?",
            "answers": [
              "297",
              "294",
              "309",
              "296"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 294."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 25 \u00d7 11?",
            "answers": [
              "270",
              "273",
              "275",
              "272"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 275."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 38 \u00d7 18?",
            "answers": [
              "684",
              "682",
              "689",
              "699"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 684."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 50 \u00d7 9?",
            "answers": [
              "450",
              "465",
              "445",
              "453"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 450."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 31 \u00d7 30?",
            "answers": [
              "915",
              "930",
              "933",
              "945"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 930."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 16 \u00d7 6?",
            "answers": [
              "106",
              "99",
              "96",
              "81"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 96."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 27 \u00d7 25?",
            "answers": [
              "685",
              "675",
              "690",
              "672"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 675."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 16?",
            "answers": [
              "190",
              "207",
              "192",
              "187"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 192."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 21 \u00d7 16?",
            "answers": [
              "346",
              "321",
              "336",
              "339"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 336."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 32 \u00d7 6?",
            "answers": [
              "191",
              "194",
              "187",
              "192"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 192."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 13 \u00d7 28?",
            "answers": [
              "374",
              "364",
              "365",
              "367"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 364."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 31 \u00d7 20?",
            "answers": [
              "635",
              "617",
              "630",
              "620"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 620."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 16 \u00d7 28?",
            "answers": [
              "449",
              "458",
              "443",
              "448"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 448."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 13 \u00d7 12?",
            "answers": [
              "166",
              "156",
              "153",
              "151"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 156."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 13 \u00d7 25?",
            "answers": [
              "315",
              "310",
              "323",
              "325"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 325."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 25 \u00d7 26?",
            "answers": [
              "653",
              "660",
              "635",
              "650"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 650."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 45 \u00d7 21?",
            "answers": [
              "943",
              "930",
              "940",
              "945"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 945."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 46 \u00d7 21?",
            "answers": [
              "964",
              "971",
              "966",
              "951"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 966."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 18 \u00d7 17?",
            "answers": [
              "305",
              "304",
              "309",
              "306"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 306."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 50 \u00d7 21?",
            "answers": [
              "1065",
              "1055",
              "1049",
              "1050"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1050."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 34 \u00d7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "466",
              "478",
              "476",
              "474"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 476."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 35 \u00d7 20?",
            "answers": [
              "697",
              "703",
              "710",
              "700"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 700."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 49 \u00d7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "688",
              "696",
              "671",
              "686"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 686."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 39 \u00d7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "546",
              "541",
              "545",
              "549"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 546."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 46 \u00d7 8?",
            "answers": [
              "373",
              "365",
              "368",
              "383"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 368."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 6?",
            "answers": [
              "56",
              "61",
              "66",
              "65"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 66."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 26 \u00d7 10?",
            "answers": [
              "245",
              "260",
              "255",
              "259"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 260."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 32 \u00d7 25?",
            "answers": [
              "800",
              "805",
              "790",
              "802"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 800."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 15 \u00d7 13?",
            "answers": [
              "195",
              "190",
              "210",
              "194"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 195."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 31 \u00d7 27?",
            "answers": [
              "822",
              "832",
              "835",
              "837"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 837."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 44 \u00d7 25?",
            "answers": [
              "1115",
              "1099",
              "1100",
              "1103"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1100."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 24 \u00d7 27?",
            "answers": [
              "658",
              "646",
              "648",
              "645"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 648."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 16 \u00d7 9?",
            "answers": [
              "142",
              "146",
              "147",
              "144"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 144."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 14 \u00d7 27?",
            "answers": [
              "376",
              "378",
              "380",
              "368"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 378."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 23 \u00d7 5?",
            "answers": [
              "130",
              "105",
              "116",
              "115"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 115."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 39 \u00d7 13?",
            "answers": [
              "507",
              "492",
              "509",
              "506"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 507."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 26 \u00d7 7?",
            "answers": [
              "184",
              "187",
              "182",
              "192"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 182."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 11?",
            "answers": [
              "110",
              "95",
              "111",
              "107"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 110."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 34 \u00d7 30?",
            "answers": [
              "1017",
              "1018",
              "1030",
              "1020"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1020."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 8?",
            "answers": [
              "89",
              "78",
              "88",
              "87"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 88."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 18 \u00d7 22?",
            "answers": [
              "401",
              "396",
              "394",
              "393"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 396."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 20 \u00d7 10?",
            "answers": [
              "200",
              "199",
              "195",
              "215"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 200."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 48 \u00d7 16?",
            "answers": [
              "773",
              "765",
              "768",
              "753"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 768."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 18?",
            "answers": [
              "183",
              "199",
              "201",
              "198"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 198."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 34 \u00d7 16?",
            "answers": [
              "544",
              "549",
              "542",
              "539"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 544."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 18 \u00d7 27?",
            "answers": [
              "486",
              "501",
              "481",
              "483"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 486."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 23 \u00d7 9?",
            "answers": [
              "207",
              "217",
              "212",
              "192"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 207."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 47 \u00d7 20?",
            "answers": [
              "930",
              "925",
              "937",
              "940"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 940."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 247 \u00f7 19?",
            "answers": [
              "13",
              "3",
              "8",
              "14"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 13."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 192 \u00f7 16?",
            "answers": [
              "22",
              "2",
              "4",
              "12"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 12."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 182 \u00f7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "3",
              "18",
              "16",
              "13"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 13."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 820 \u00f7 20?",
            "answers": [
              "40",
              "38",
              "41",
              "56"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 41."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 77 \u00f7 7?",
            "answers": [
              "12",
              "21",
              "5",
              "11"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 11."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 12 \u00f7 2?",
            "answers": [
              "5",
              "16",
              "6",
              "8"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 6."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 420 \u00f7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "45",
              "30",
              "29",
              "35"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 30."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 114 \u00f7 6?",
            "answers": [
              "19",
              "34",
              "20",
              "17"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 19."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 1250 \u00f7 25?",
            "answers": [
              "53",
              "50",
              "40",
              "48"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 50."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 84 \u00f7 2?",
            "answers": [
              "43",
              "41",
              "47",
              "42"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 42."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 154 \u00f7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "6",
              "11",
              "21",
              "26"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 11."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 102 \u00f7 17?",
            "answers": [
              "8",
              "16",
              "6",
              "5"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 6."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 387 \u00f7 9?",
            "answers": [
              "43",
              "58",
              "40",
              "48"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 43."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 480 \u00f7 10?",
            "answers": [
              "48",
              "49",
              "58",
              "47"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 48."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 504 \u00f7 18?",
            "answers": [
              "28",
              "43",
              "30",
              "23"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 28."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 567 \u00f7 21?",
            "answers": [
              "37",
              "26",
              "27",
              "24"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 27."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 286 \u00f7 11?",
            "answers": [
              "41",
              "26",
              "27",
              "31"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 26."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 52 \u00f7 2?",
            "answers": [
              "29",
              "26",
              "28",
              "11"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 26."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 480 \u00f7 24?",
            "answers": [
              "21",
              "25",
              "17",
              "20"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 20."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 912 \u00f7 24?",
            "answers": [
              "23",
              "38",
              "36",
              "28"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 38."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 250 \u00f7 10?",
            "answers": [
              "26",
              "40",
              "25",
              "35"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 25."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 374 \u00f7 17?",
            "answers": [
              "22",
              "7",
              "23",
              "19"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 22."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 168 \u00f7 24?",
            "answers": [
              "7",
              "9",
              "4",
              "22"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 7."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 80 \u00f7 16?",
            "answers": [
              "11",
              "4",
              "6",
              "5"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 5."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 384 \u00f7 8?",
            "answers": [
              "46",
              "51",
              "48",
              "47"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 48."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 456 \u00f7 12?",
            "answers": [
              "36",
              "41",
              "38",
              "43"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 38."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 396 \u00f7 9?",
            "answers": [
              "44",
              "46",
              "41",
              "59"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 44."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 300 \u00f7 15?",
            "answers": [
              "30",
              "10",
              "20",
              "5"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 20."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 228 \u00f7 6?",
            "answers": [
              "43",
              "37",
              "38",
              "53"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 38."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 242 \u00f7 22?",
            "answers": [
              "26",
              "11",
              "12",
              "13"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 11."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 140 \u00f7 4?",
            "answers": [
              "35",
              "40",
              "36",
              "20"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 35."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 216 \u00f7 24?",
            "answers": [
              "7",
              "6",
              "11",
              "9"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 9."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 102 \u00f7 3?",
            "answers": [
              "34",
              "19",
              "33",
              "39"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 34."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 150 \u00f7 15?",
            "answers": [
              "15",
              "0",
              "10",
              "25"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 10."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 470 \u00f7 10?",
            "answers": [
              "46",
              "47",
              "32",
              "44"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 47."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 117 \u00f7 3?",
            "answers": [
              "44",
              "36",
              "39",
              "41"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 39."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 360 \u00f7 10?",
            "answers": [
              "34",
              "36",
              "51",
              "38"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 36."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 882 \u00f7 21?",
            "answers": [
              "42",
              "39",
              "57",
              "27"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 42."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 760 \u00f7 19?",
            "answers": [
              "37",
              "41",
              "25",
              "40"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 40."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 448 \u00f7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "33",
              "47",
              "32",
              "35"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 32."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 966 \u00f7 21?",
            "answers": [
              "46",
              "49",
              "36",
              "31"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 46."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 150 \u00f7 10?",
            "answers": [
              "18",
              "15",
              "25",
              "30"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 15."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 648 \u00f7 24?",
            "answers": [
              "32",
              "22",
              "27",
              "30"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 27."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 418 \u00f7 22?",
            "answers": [
              "20",
              "17",
              "29",
              "19"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 19."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 864 \u00f7 24?",
            "answers": [
              "36",
              "41",
              "35",
              "51"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 36."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 93 \u00f7 3?",
            "answers": [
              "29",
              "21",
              "31",
              "16"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 31."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 84 \u00f7 12?",
            "answers": [
              "4",
              "7",
              "10",
              "17"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 7."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 44 \u00f7 4?",
            "answers": [
              "1",
              "21",
              "11",
              "13"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 11."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 264 \u00f7 22?",
            "answers": [
              "22",
              "11",
              "12",
              "7"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 12."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 792 \u00f7 18?",
            "answers": [
              "44",
              "42",
              "43",
              "59"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 44."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 493 \u00f7 17?",
            "answers": [
              "19",
              "14",
              "29",
              "44"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 29."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 374 \u00f7 22?",
            "answers": [
              "27",
              "7",
              "17",
              "2"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 17."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 376 \u00f7 8?",
            "answers": [
              "52",
              "47",
              "42",
              "37"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 47."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 836 \u00f7 22?",
            "answers": [
              "43",
              "48",
              "38",
              "33"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 38."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 720 \u00f7 24?",
            "answers": [
              "40",
              "31",
              "30",
              "15"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 30."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 456 \u00f7 24?",
            "answers": [
              "19",
              "16",
              "9",
              "29"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 19."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 234 \u00f7 13?",
            "answers": [
              "3",
              "18",
              "19",
              "21"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 18."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 81 \u00f7 9?",
            "answers": [
              "2",
              "24",
              "7",
              "9"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 9."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 486 \u00f7 18?",
            "answers": [
              "12",
              "22",
              "32",
              "27"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 27."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 192 \u00f7 16?",
            "answers": [
              "12",
              "11",
              "22",
              "2"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 12."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 132 \u00f7 22?",
            "answers": [
              "9",
              "6",
              "16",
              "11"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 6."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 338 \u00f7 13?",
            "answers": [
              "26",
              "24",
              "36",
              "23"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 26."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 483 \u00f7 23?",
            "answers": [
              "11",
              "19",
              "16",
              "21"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 21."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 288 \u00f7 16?",
            "answers": [
              "18",
              "33",
              "15",
              "20"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 18."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 140 \u00f7 7?",
            "answers": [
              "5",
              "15",
              "35",
              "20"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 20."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 204 \u00f7 6?",
            "answers": [
              "33",
              "34",
              "32",
              "37"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 34."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 319 \u00f7 11?",
            "answers": [
              "26",
              "31",
              "34",
              "29"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 29."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 320 \u00f7 20?",
            "answers": [
              "1",
              "14",
              "16",
              "31"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 16."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 205 \u00f7 5?",
            "answers": [
              "31",
              "36",
              "41",
              "44"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 41."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 63 \u00f7 7?",
            "answers": [
              "6",
              "9",
              "8",
              "7"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 9."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 240 \u00f7 5?",
            "answers": [
              "63",
              "51",
              "43",
              "48"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 48."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 152 \u00f7 19?",
            "answers": [
              "8",
              "5",
              "6",
              "11"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 8."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 180 \u00f7 12?",
            "answers": [
              "25",
              "13",
              "15",
              "10"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 15."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 476 \u00f7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "24",
              "49",
              "34",
              "37"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 34."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 210 \u00f7 5?",
            "answers": [
              "42",
              "32",
              "47",
              "39"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 42."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 175 \u00f7 5?",
            "answers": [
              "50",
              "35",
              "33",
              "38"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 35."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 940 \u00f7 20?",
            "answers": [
              "47",
              "45",
              "32",
              "44"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 47."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 775 \u00f7 25?",
            "answers": [
              "29",
              "30",
              "31",
              "41"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 31."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 738 \u00f7 18?",
            "answers": [
              "56",
              "39",
              "41",
              "42"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 41."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 171 \u00f7 19?",
            "answers": [
              "7",
              "8",
              "9",
              "6"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 9."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 96 \u00f7 16?",
            "answers": [
              "21",
              "1",
              "6",
              "11"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 6."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 476 \u00f7 17?",
            "answers": [
              "33",
              "43",
              "28",
              "13"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 28."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 574 \u00f7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "36",
              "41",
              "39",
              "40"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 41."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 184 \u00f7 23?",
            "answers": [
              "8",
              "18",
              "10",
              "23"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 8."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 324 \u00f7 12?",
            "answers": [
              "30",
              "29",
              "27",
              "37"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 27."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 370 \u00f7 10?",
            "answers": [
              "37",
              "34",
              "42",
              "36"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 37."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 138 \u00f7 3?",
            "answers": [
              "51",
              "41",
              "47",
              "46"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 46."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 126 \u00f7 18?",
            "answers": [
              "9",
              "7",
              "5",
              "22"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 7."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 216 \u00f7 18?",
            "answers": [
              "27",
              "15",
              "14",
              "12"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 12."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 315 \u00f7 21?",
            "answers": [
              "10",
              "15",
              "12",
              "20"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 15."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 450 \u00f7 25?",
            "answers": [
              "23",
              "18",
              "21",
              "19"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 18."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 208 \u00f7 8?",
            "answers": [
              "23",
              "25",
              "26",
              "29"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 26."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 285 \u00f7 15?",
            "answers": [
              "18",
              "21",
              "16",
              "19"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 19."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 270 \u00f7 18?",
            "answers": [
              "14",
              "30",
              "0",
              "15"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 15."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 987 \u00f7 21?",
            "answers": [
              "52",
              "47",
              "57",
              "44"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 47."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 264 \u00f7 8?",
            "answers": [
              "48",
              "28",
              "33",
              "32"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 33."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 112 \u00f7 16?",
            "answers": [
              "5",
              "12",
              "4",
              "7"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 7."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 342 \u00f7 19?",
            "answers": [
              "19",
              "18",
              "16",
              "20"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 18."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 30 \u00f7 3?",
            "answers": [
              "10",
              "9",
              "8",
              "25"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 10."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 589 \u00f7 19?",
            "answers": [
              "21",
              "31",
              "30",
              "26"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 31."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 1100 \u00f7 25?",
            "answers": [
              "39",
              "47",
              "54",
              "44"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 44."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 504 \u00f7 18?",
            "answers": [
              "30",
              "43",
              "28",
              "33"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 28."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 42 \u00f7 2?",
            "answers": [
              "11",
              "16",
              "21",
              "36"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 21."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 638 \u00f7 22?",
            "answers": [
              "44",
              "30",
              "26",
              "29"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 29."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 102 \u00f7 6?",
            "answers": [
              "32",
              "19",
              "17",
              "2"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 17."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 510 \u00f7 17?",
            "answers": [
              "15",
              "30",
              "27",
              "32"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 30."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 315 \u00f7 21?",
            "answers": [
              "20",
              "15",
              "13",
              "14"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 15."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 374 \u00f7 17?",
            "answers": [
              "12",
              "22",
              "24",
              "27"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 22."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 637 \u00f7 13?",
            "answers": [
              "59",
              "44",
              "51",
              "49"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 49."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 250 \u00f7 5?",
            "answers": [
              "50",
              "60",
              "49",
              "52"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 50."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 513 \u00f7 19?",
            "answers": [
              "42",
              "27",
              "30",
              "25"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 27."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 114 \u00f7 6?",
            "answers": [
              "21",
              "19",
              "22",
              "18"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 19."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 900 \u00f7 20?",
            "answers": [
              "42",
              "45",
              "35",
              "48"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 45."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 18 \u00f7 3?",
            "answers": [
              "6",
              "10",
              "1",
              "16"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 6."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 1000 \u00f7 25?",
            "answers": [
              "37",
              "41",
              "38",
              "40"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 40."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 442 \u00f7 17?",
            "answers": [
              "36",
              "26",
              "16",
              "28"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 26."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 475 \u00f7 25?",
            "answers": [
              "16",
              "4",
              "21",
              "19"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 19."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 360 \u00f7 8?",
            "answers": [
              "44",
              "45",
              "55",
              "43"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 45."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 144 \u00f7 16?",
            "answers": [
              "7",
              "9",
              "12",
              "24"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 9."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 87 \u00f7 3?",
            "answers": [
              "34",
              "19",
              "29",
              "26"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 29."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 851 \u00f7 23?",
            "answers": [
              "27",
              "39",
              "37",
              "40"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 37."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 216 \u00f7 18?",
            "answers": [
              "10",
              "12",
              "4",
              "13"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 12."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 361 \u00f7 19?",
            "answers": [
              "29",
              "19",
              "24",
              "14"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 19."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 936 \u00f7 24?",
            "answers": [
              "36",
              "24",
              "39",
              "41"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 39."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 192 \u00f7 4?",
            "answers": [
              "50",
              "63",
              "48",
              "46"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 48."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 364 \u00f7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "11",
              "26",
              "36",
              "31"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 26."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 819 \u00f7 21?",
            "answers": [
              "39",
              "40",
              "37",
              "49"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 39."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 140 \u00f7 7?",
            "answers": [
              "5",
              "20",
              "21",
              "35"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 20."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 585 \u00f7 15?",
            "answers": [
              "42",
              "44",
              "49",
              "39"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 39."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 517 \u00f7 11?",
            "answers": [
              "32",
              "47",
              "62",
              "52"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 47."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 154 \u00f7 22?",
            "answers": [
              "7",
              "22",
              "12",
              "17"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 7."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 943 \u00f7 23?",
            "answers": [
              "40",
              "56",
              "41",
              "46"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 41."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 42 \u00f7 2?",
            "answers": [
              "11",
              "19",
              "20",
              "21"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 21."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 95 \u00f7 5?",
            "answers": [
              "22",
              "9",
              "19",
              "14"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 19."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 136 \u00f7 17?",
            "answers": [
              "10",
              "9",
              "8",
              "23"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 8."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 111 \u00f7 3?",
            "answers": [
              "22",
              "32",
              "37",
              "52"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 37."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 276 \u00f7 6?",
            "answers": [
              "46",
              "41",
              "47",
              "51"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 46."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 882 \u00f7 21?",
            "answers": [
              "47",
              "32",
              "57",
              "42"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 42."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 75 \u00f7 3?",
            "answers": [
              "23",
              "40",
              "25",
              "20"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 25."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 77 \u00f7 7?",
            "answers": [
              "1",
              "16",
              "26",
              "11"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 11."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 533 \u00f7 13?",
            "answers": [
              "41",
              "42",
              "43",
              "39"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 41."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 105 \u00f7 3?",
            "answers": [
              "35",
              "36",
              "45",
              "34"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 35."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 450 \u00f7 25?",
            "answers": [
              "28",
              "19",
              "13",
              "18"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 18."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 552 \u00f7 23?",
            "answers": [
              "29",
              "26",
              "34",
              "24"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 24."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 600 \u00f7 20?",
            "answers": [
              "40",
              "28",
              "30",
              "32"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 30."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 63 \u00f7 9?",
            "answers": [
              "10",
              "7",
              "4",
              "2"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 7."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 799 \u00f7 17?",
            "answers": [
              "47",
              "48",
              "62",
              "45"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 47."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 288 \u00f7 9?",
            "answers": [
              "32",
              "34",
              "17",
              "47"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 32."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 182 \u00f7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "16",
              "28",
              "13",
              "15"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 13."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 154 \u00f7 11?",
            "answers": [
              "9",
              "15",
              "19",
              "14"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 14."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 574 \u00f7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "41",
              "39",
              "36",
              "26"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 41."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 602 \u00f7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "43",
              "46",
              "53",
              "38"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 43."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 288 \u00f7 24?",
            "answers": [
              "4",
              "13",
              "12",
              "2"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 12."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 630 \u00f7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "60",
              "30",
              "45",
              "42"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 45."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 250 \u00f7 25?",
            "answers": [
              "15",
              "10",
              "5",
              "0"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 10."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 432 \u00f7 16?",
            "answers": [
              "30",
              "42",
              "12",
              "27"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 27."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 672 \u00f7 14?",
            "answers": [
              "47",
              "48",
              "58",
              "43"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 48."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 110 \u00f7 10?",
            "answers": [
              "9",
              "26",
              "5",
              "11"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 11."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 88 \u00f7 8?",
            "answers": [
              "9",
              "21",
              "11",
              "13"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 11."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 1058 \u00f7 23?",
            "answers": [
              "31",
              "48",
              "45",
              "46"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 46."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 44 \u00f7 2?",
            "answers": [
              "22",
              "21",
              "12",
              "37"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 22."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 722 \u00f7 19?",
            "answers": [
              "35",
              "38",
              "53",
              "28"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 38."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 126 \u00f7 3?",
            "answers": [
              "37",
              "45",
              "40",
              "42"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 42."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 338 \u00f7 13?",
            "answers": [
              "31",
              "26",
              "11",
              "29"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 26."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 72 \u00f7 3?",
            "answers": [
              "27",
              "21",
              "24",
              "34"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 24."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 646 \u00f7 19?",
            "answers": [
              "24",
              "34",
              "32",
              "44"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 34."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 235 \u00f7 5?",
            "answers": [
              "50",
              "32",
              "62",
              "47"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 47."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 572 \u00f7 22?",
            "answers": [
              "26",
              "11",
              "24",
              "31"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 26."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 220 \u00f7 20?",
            "answers": [
              "12",
              "11",
              "6",
              "9"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 11."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 110 \u00f7 5?",
            "answers": [
              "17",
              "22",
              "20",
              "27"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 22."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 221 \u00f7 13?",
            "answers": [
              "16",
              "17",
              "2",
              "7"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 17."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 80 \u00f7 2?",
            "answers": [
              "40",
              "35",
              "39",
              "30"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 40."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 255 \u00f7 15?",
            "answers": [
              "17",
              "16",
              "7",
              "19"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 17."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 200 \u00f7 20?",
            "answers": [
              "0",
              "9",
              "10",
              "15"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 10."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 1058 \u00f7 23?",
            "answers": [
              "45",
              "49",
              "44",
              "46"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 46."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 50 \u00f7 10?",
            "answers": [
              "8",
              "2",
              "11",
              "5"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 5."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 588 \u00f7 12?",
            "answers": [
              "52",
              "49",
              "44",
              "64"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 49."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 264 \u00f7 6?",
            "answers": [
              "44",
              "42",
              "49",
              "47"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 44."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 510 \u00f7 17?",
            "answers": [
              "30",
              "32",
              "33",
              "28"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 30."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 828 \u00f7 23?",
            "answers": [
              "51",
              "34",
              "38",
              "36"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 36."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 432 \u00f7 24?",
            "answers": [
              "21",
              "19",
              "18",
              "3"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 18."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 1008 \u00f7 24?",
            "answers": [
              "47",
              "41",
              "42",
              "32"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 42."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 667 \u00f7 23?",
            "answers": [
              "39",
              "34",
              "14",
              "29"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 29."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 54 \u00f7 2?",
            "answers": [
              "27",
              "29",
              "25",
              "42"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 27."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 315 \u00f7 7?",
            "answers": [
              "42",
              "45",
              "30",
              "40"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 45."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 1032 \u00f7 24?",
            "answers": [
              "43",
              "48",
              "40",
              "41"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 43."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 143 \u00f7 13?",
            "answers": [
              "11",
              "10",
              "13",
              "16"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 11."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 480 \u00f7 10?",
            "answers": [
              "50",
              "48",
              "53",
              "63"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 48."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 372 \u00f7 12?",
            "answers": [
              "31",
              "46",
              "29",
              "36"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 31."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 72 \u00f7 3?",
            "answers": [
              "14",
              "21",
              "19",
              "24"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 24."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 792 \u00f7 24?",
            "answers": [
              "35",
              "31",
              "33",
              "18"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 33."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 672 \u00f7 16?",
            "answers": [
              "44",
              "42",
              "39",
              "41"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 42."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 437 \u00f7 23?",
            "answers": [
              "17",
              "18",
              "21",
              "19"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 19."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 510 \u00f7 17?",
            "answers": [
              "25",
              "30",
              "28",
              "31"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 30."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 88 \u00f7 4?",
            "answers": [
              "22",
              "7",
              "27",
              "17"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 22."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 456 \u00f7 12?",
            "answers": [
              "43",
              "36",
              "38",
              "40"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 38."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 492 \u00f7 12?",
            "answers": [
              "56",
              "46",
              "44",
              "41"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 41."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 315 \u00f7 21?",
            "answers": [
              "12",
              "25",
              "10",
              "15"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 15."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 72 \u00f7 12?",
            "answers": [
              "5",
              "11",
              "16",
              "6"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 6."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 552 \u00f7 12?",
            "answers": [
              "31",
              "47",
              "48",
              "46"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 46."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 9 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "729",
              "732",
              "744",
              "728"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 729."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 3 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "25",
              "28",
              "17",
              "27"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 27."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 7 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "2406",
              "2386",
              "2416",
              "2401"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 2401."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 2 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "26",
              "17",
              "19",
              "16"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 16."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 5 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "135",
              "110",
              "125",
              "140"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 125."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 9 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "6563",
              "6561",
              "6564",
              "6571"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 6561."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 2 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "8",
              "11",
              "18",
              "6"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 8."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 4 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "255",
              "256",
              "258",
              "246"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 256."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 6 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "41",
              "36",
              "33",
              "51"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 36."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 9 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "79",
              "86",
              "81",
              "78"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 81."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 8 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "67",
              "64",
              "59",
              "61"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 64."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 8 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "64",
              "74",
              "54",
              "59"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 64."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 7 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "2401",
              "2403",
              "2404",
              "2411"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 2401."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 8 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "61",
              "64",
              "69",
              "79"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 64."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 4 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "21",
              "15",
              "14",
              "16"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 16."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 6 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "1281",
              "1311",
              "1296",
              "1291"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1296."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 10 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "100",
              "115",
              "103",
              "98"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 100."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 9 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "714",
              "729",
              "726",
              "728"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 729."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 7 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "44",
              "49",
              "39",
              "64"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 49."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 5 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "25",
              "26",
              "40",
              "28"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 25."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 7 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "2399",
              "2401",
              "2406",
              "2416"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 2401."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 7 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "52",
              "49",
              "47",
              "48"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 49."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 8 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "4096",
              "4106",
              "4101",
              "4094"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 4096."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 7 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "34",
              "47",
              "44",
              "49"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 49."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 4 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "14",
              "11",
              "16",
              "18"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 16."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 6 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "38",
              "31",
              "36",
              "26"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 36."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 8 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "64",
              "67",
              "61",
              "79"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 64."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 5 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "120",
              "125",
              "127",
              "126"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 125."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 7 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "34",
              "54",
              "49",
              "47"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 49."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 7 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "2396",
              "2406",
              "2401",
              "2386"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 2401."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 6 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "51",
              "36",
              "31",
              "37"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 36."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 2 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "7",
              "6",
              "4",
              "1"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 4."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 3 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "79",
              "81",
              "91",
              "84"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 81."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 3 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "37",
              "32",
              "27",
              "25"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 27."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 5 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "20",
              "26",
              "25",
              "24"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 25."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 9 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "81",
              "96",
              "82",
              "79"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 81."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 5 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "625",
              "628",
              "635",
              "623"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 625."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 9 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "730",
              "744",
              "726",
              "729"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 729."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 7 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "54",
              "50",
              "49",
              "51"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 49."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 8 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "522",
              "517",
              "513",
              "512"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 512."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 2 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "31",
              "17",
              "16",
              "21"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 16."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 5 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "115",
              "125",
              "126",
              "140"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 125."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 8 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "4101",
              "4097",
              "4099",
              "4096"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 4096."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 9 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "6561",
              "6566",
              "6551",
              "6564"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 6561."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 8 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "4081",
              "4096",
              "4095",
              "4098"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 4096."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 10 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "997",
              "1000",
              "1002",
              "1003"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1000."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 10 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "1000",
              "998",
              "997",
              "1003"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1000."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 5 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "25",
              "24",
              "10",
              "20"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 25."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 5 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "120",
              "127",
              "122",
              "125"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 125."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 4 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "17",
              "16",
              "19",
              "18"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 16."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 5 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "23",
              "27",
              "15",
              "25"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 25."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 9 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "744",
              "728",
              "729",
              "732"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 729."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 10 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "1001",
              "1000",
              "1003",
              "985"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1000."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 5 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "10",
              "28",
              "25",
              "20"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 25."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 8 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "54",
              "63",
              "64",
              "59"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 64."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 2 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "13",
              "18",
              "16",
              "15"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 16."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 6 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "35",
              "36",
              "41",
              "21"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 36."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 5 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "23",
              "28",
              "20",
              "25"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 25."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 9 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "719",
              "730",
              "729",
              "739"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 729."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 10 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "1010",
              "1003",
              "1000",
              "1005"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1000."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 10 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "998",
              "1010",
              "1005",
              "1000"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1000."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 2 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "19",
              "1",
              "14",
              "4"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 4."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 2 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "14",
              "19",
              "12",
              "4"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 4."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 10 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "9999",
              "10005",
              "10000",
              "9990"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 10000."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 9 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "719",
              "726",
              "734",
              "729"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 729."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 2 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "26",
              "16",
              "21",
              "15"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 16."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 7 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "2401",
              "2404",
              "2386",
              "2400"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 2401."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 7 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "47",
              "49",
              "59",
              "39"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 49."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 4 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "21",
              "1",
              "26",
              "16"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 16."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 5 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "25",
              "15",
              "27",
              "40"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 25."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 5 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "27",
              "10",
              "35",
              "25"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 25."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 7 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "343",
              "344",
              "333",
              "342"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 343."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 3 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "32",
              "22",
              "27",
              "37"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 27."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 5 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "124",
              "125",
              "126",
              "130"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 125."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 10 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "10015",
              "10000",
              "10002",
              "9997"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 10000."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 5 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "610",
              "625",
              "635",
              "624"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 625."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 10 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "90",
              "105",
              "85",
              "100"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 100."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 3 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "2",
              "9",
              "4",
              "10"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 9."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 4 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "65",
              "64",
              "62",
              "79"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 64."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 7 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "346",
              "343",
              "342",
              "341"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 343."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 5 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "625",
              "627",
              "628",
              "635"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 625."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 4 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "241",
              "256",
              "266",
              "261"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 256."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 2 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "1",
              "4",
              "3",
              "5"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 4."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 4 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "271",
              "261",
              "256",
              "253"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 256."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 4 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "64",
              "62",
              "49",
              "74"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 64."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 6 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "36",
              "38",
              "26",
              "35"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 36."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 5 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "625",
              "615",
              "627",
              "624"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 625."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 2 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "11",
              "13",
              "5",
              "8"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 8."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 7 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "2401",
              "2399",
              "2386",
              "2402"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 2401."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 10 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "985",
              "995",
              "999",
              "1000"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1000."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "What is 8 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "509",
              "512",
              "522",
              "507"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 512."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 2 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "3",
              "2",
              "4",
              "1"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 4."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 6 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "226",
              "215",
              "218",
              "216"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 216."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 6 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "1311",
              "1306",
              "1296",
              "1286"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 1296."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 4 to the power of 3?",
            "answers": [
              "64",
              "62",
              "67",
              "65"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 64."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 9 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "81",
              "71",
              "66",
              "84"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 81."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 2 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "2",
              "5",
              "14",
              "4"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 4."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 3 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "9",
              "7",
              "2",
              "11"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 9."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 5 to the power of 4?",
            "answers": [
              "624",
              "627",
              "625",
              "623"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 625."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 2 to the power of 2?",
            "answers": [
              "9",
              "7",
              "4",
              "19"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
            "explanation": "The correct answer is 4."
          }
        ]
      ]
    ],
    "medium": [
      [ // Set 1
        { "question": "What is the value of x if 2x + 5 = 15?", "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "10"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Subtract 5 from both sides to get 2x = 10, then divide by 2 to get x = 5." },
        { "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with a width of 5 units and a length of 8 units?", "answers": ["13 square units", "30 square units", "40 square units", "45 square units"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "The area of a rectangle is width times length (5 * 8 = 40)." },
        { "question": "What is 15% of 200?", "answers": ["15", "20", "30", "40"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "15% of 200 is (15/100) * 200, which equals 30." },
        { "question": "What is the square root of 144?", "answers": ["10", "11", "12", "13"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "The square root of 144 is 12, because 12 * 12 = 144." },
        { "question": "What is the next prime number after 13?", "answers": ["14", "15", "16", "17"], "correctAnswerIndex": 3, "explanation": "A prime number is only divisible by 1 and itself. 17 is the next prime number after 13." },
        { "question": "Solve for y: 3y - 4 = 11", "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Add 4 to both sides (3y = 15), then divide by 3 to get y = 5." },
        { "question": "What is the perimeter of a square with a side length of 7 cm?", "answers": ["14 cm", "21 cm", "28 cm", "49 cm"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "The perimeter of a square is 4 times the side length (4 * 7 = 28)." },
        { "question": "Simplify the fraction 12/18.", "answers": ["1/2", "2/3", "3/4", "5/6"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Both 12 and 18 are divisible by 6. 12/6 = 2 and 18/6 = 3, so the fraction simplifies to 2/3." },
        { "question": "If a train travels at 60 mph, how far will it travel in 2.5 hours?", "answers": ["120 miles", "150 miles", "180 miles", "200 miles"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Distance = Speed × Time. 60 mph * 2.5 hours = 150 miles." },
        { "question": "What is 5 factorial (5!)?", "answers": ["25", "60", "120", "720"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "5! = 5 × 4 × 3 × 2 × 1 = 120." }
      ]
    ],
    "hard": [
       [ // Set 1
        { "question": "What is the derivative of x^3 with respect to x?", "answers": ["3x", "x^2", "3x^2", "3x^3"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Using the power rule, the derivative of x^n is nx^(n-1). So, the derivative of x^3 is 3x^2." },
        { "question": "What is the integral of 2x dx?", "answers": ["x^2 + C", "2x^2 + C", "x^3 + C", "2 + C"], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "The integral of 2x with respect to x is x^2, plus the constant of integration, C." },
        { "question": "What is the value of log_10(1000)?", "answers": ["2", "3", "4", "10"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "log_10(1000) asks '10 to what power equals 1000?'. 10^3 = 1000, so the answer is 3." },
        { "question": "In a right-angled triangle, if the two shorter sides are 3cm and 4cm, what is the length of the hypotenuse?", "answers": ["5cm", "6cm", "7cm", "8cm"], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "According to the Pythagorean theorem (a^2 + b^2 = c^2), 3^2 + 4^2 = 9 + 16 = 25. The square root of 25 is 5." },
        { "question": "What is the imaginary unit 'i' squared (i^2)?", "answers": ["1", "-1", "i", "-i"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "The imaginary unit 'i' is defined as the square root of -1. Therefore, i^2 = -1." },
        { "question": "What is the sum of the angles in a hexagon?", "answers": ["360 degrees", "540 degrees", "720 degrees", "900 degrees"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "The sum of the interior angles of an n-sided polygon is given by the formula (n-2) * 180. For a hexagon (n=6), this is (6-2) * 180 = 720 degrees." },
        { "question": "Solve the quadratic equation: x^2 - 5x + 6 = 0", "answers": ["x=2, x=3", "x=1, x=6", "x=-2, x=-3", "x=5, x=1"], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "The equation can be factored into (x-2)(x-3) = 0, which gives the solutions x=2 and x=3." },
        { "question": "What is the value of e^(iπ) + 1?", "answers": ["0", "1", "2", "π"], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "This is Euler's identity, a famous equation in mathematics. e^(iπ) = -1, so e^(iπ) + 1 = 0." },
        { "question": "How many permutations are there of the letters in the word 'APPLE'?", "answers": ["24", "60", "120", "25"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "The word has 5 letters, but the letter 'P' is repeated twice. The formula is 5! / 2! = 120 / 2 = 60." },
        { "question": "What is the limit of (1 + 1/n)^n as n approaches infinity?", "answers": ["1", "0", "e", "infinity"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "This is the definition of the mathematical constant 'e', which is approximately 2.718." }
      ]
    ]
  },
  "english": {
    "easy": [
      [ // Set 1
        { "question": "Which word is a synonym for 'happy'?", "answers": ["Sad", "Angry", "Joyful", "Tired"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "'Joyful' means feeling, expressing, or causing great pleasure and happiness." },
        { "question": "What is the plural of 'mouse'?", "answers": ["Mouses", "Mice", "Mouse", "Mooses"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "The plural form of 'mouse' is an irregular plural, 'mice'." },
        { "question": "Identify the noun in the sentence: 'The cat sat on the mat.'", "answers": ["The", "sat", "on", "cat"], "correctAnswerIndex": 3, "explanation": "A noun is a word that represents a person, place, thing, or idea. 'Cat' is a thing." },
        { "question": "What is the opposite of 'hot'?", "answers": ["Warm", "Cold", "Spicy", "Sunny"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "'Cold' is the antonym for 'hot'." },
        { "question": "Which sentence is grammatically correct?", "answers": ["She go to school.", "She goes to school.", "She going to school.", "She goed to school."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "For a third-person singular subject ('She'), the verb 'go' must be in the form 'goes'." },
        { "question": "What punctuation mark is used at the end of a question?", "answers": ["Period (.)", "Comma (,)", "Exclamation mark (!)", "Question mark (?)"], "correctAnswerIndex": 3, "explanation": "A question mark is used to indicate an interrogative clause or phrase in many languages." },
        { "question": "Choose the correct spelling:", "answers": [" recieve", "receive", "reiceve", "receeve"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "The correct spelling is 'receive'." },
        { "question": "What is the past tense of the verb 'run'?", "answers": ["Runned", "Ran", "Running", "Runs"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "'Ran' is the simple past tense of 'run'." },
        { "question": "Which of these is a pronoun?", "answers": ["House", "Jump", "They", "Quickly"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "A pronoun is a word that is used instead of a noun or noun phrase. 'They' is a pronoun." },
        { "question": "Complete the sentence: 'An apple a day keeps the ______ away.'", "answers": ["teacher", "friend", "doctor", "rain"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "This is a common proverb suggesting that eating fruit maintains good health." }
      ]
    ],
    "medium": [
      [ // Set 1
        { "question": "What is a metaphor?", "answers": ["A comparison using 'like' or 'as'", "Giving human qualities to non-human things", "A direct comparison between two unlike things", "An extreme exaggeration"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "A metaphor is a figure of speech that directly equates two unlike things without using 'like' or 'as'." },
        { "question": "In which point of view is the narrator a character in the story, referring to themselves as 'I'?", "answers": ["First-person", "Second-person", "Third-person limited", "Third-person omniscient"], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "First-person narrative is a point of view where the story is narrated by one character at a time." },
        { "question": "What does the idiom 'bite the bullet' mean?", "answers": ["To eat something very hard", "To get shot", "To endure a difficult situation with courage", "To go to the dentist"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "The idiom means to face a difficult or unpleasant situation with determination and bravery." },
        { "question": "Identify the adjective in the sentence: 'The beautiful flowers bloomed.'", "answers": ["The", "beautiful", "flowers", "bloomed"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "An adjective is a word that describes a noun. 'Beautiful' describes the 'flowers'." },
        { "question": "Who wrote the play 'Romeo and Juliet'?", "answers": ["Charles Dickens", "Jane Austen", "William Shakespeare", "Mark Twain"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "'Romeo and Juliet' is a famous tragedy written by William Shakespeare." },
        { "question": "What is the main difference between 'its' and 'it's'?", "answers": ["They are interchangeable", "'Its' is possessive, 'it's' is a contraction of 'it is'", "'It's' is possessive, 'its' is a contraction of 'it is'", "There is no difference"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "'Its' shows ownership (The dog wagged its tail), while 'it's' is a shortened form of 'it is' or 'it has' (It's a beautiful day)." },
        { "question": "What is alliteration?", "answers": ["The repetition of vowel sounds", "The repetition of consonant sounds at the beginning of words", "A word that imitates a sound", "A pattern of rhyming words"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Alliteration is the occurrence of the same letter or sound at the beginning of adjacent or closely connected words (e.g., 'sweet birds sang')." },
        { "question": "What is the theme of a story?", "answers": ["The plot or sequence of events", "The time and place where the story occurs", "The main character", "The underlying message or main idea"], "correctAnswerIndex": 3, "explanation": "The theme is the central topic, subject, or message within a narrative." },
        { "question": "Which of the following is a complex sentence?", "answers": ["The dog barked.", "The dog barked and the cat ran away.", "Because the dog barked, the cat ran away.", "The big, brown dog barked loudly."], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "A complex sentence has an independent clause and at least one dependent clause. 'Because the dog barked' is a dependent clause." },
        { "question": "What does 'e.g.' stand for?", "answers": ["And so on", "For example", "In other words", "That is"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "e.g. is an abbreviation for the Latin phrase 'exempli gratia', which means 'for example'." }
      ]
    ],
    "hard": [
      [ // Set 1
        { "question": "What is a 'soliloquy' in a play?", "answers": ["A conversation between two characters", "A speech given by a character to the audience or themselves, revealing their thoughts", "The final speech in a play", "A short, witty comment"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "A soliloquy is a device often used in drama when a character speaks to themselves, relating thoughts and feelings, thereby also sharing them with the audience." },
        { "question": "Who is the author of the epic poem 'Paradise Lost'?", "answers": ["Geoffrey Chaucer", "John Donne", "John Milton", "Alexander Pope"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "'Paradise Lost' is an epic poem in blank verse by the 17th-century English poet John Milton." },
        { "question": "What is the literary term for a story that can be interpreted to reveal a hidden meaning, typically a moral or political one?", "answers": ["Allegory", "Satire", "Parody", "Fable"], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "An allegory is a story, poem, or picture that can be interpreted to reveal a hidden meaning. George Orwell's 'Animal Farm' is a famous example." },
        { "question": "What is iambic pentameter?", "answers": ["A line of verse with five metrical feet, each consisting of one long syllable followed by one short syllable", "A line of verse with ten syllables", "A line of verse with five metrical feet, each consisting of one short syllable followed by one long syllable", "A type of rhyme scheme"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Iambic pentameter is a type of metric line used in traditional English poetry and verse drama. The term describes the rhythm that the words establish in that line, which is measured in small groups of syllables called 'feet'." },
        { "question": "In literary criticism, what does 'dystopia' refer to?", "answers": ["A perfect, ideal society", "A story set in the future", "An imagined state or society in which there is great suffering or injustice", "A story with a sad ending"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "A dystopia is a community or society that is undesirable or frightening. It is often characterized by dehumanization, totalitarian governments, and environmental disaster. 'Brave New World' and '1984' are classic dystopian novels." },
        { "question": "Which literary movement, popular in the late 18th and early 19th centuries, emphasized emotion, individualism, and the glorification of nature?", "answers": ["Realism", "Modernism", "Romanticism", "The Enlightenment"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Romanticism was an artistic, literary, musical and intellectual movement that originated in Europe toward the end of the 18th century." },
        { "question": "What is a 'non sequitur'?", "answers": ["A conclusion or statement that does not logically follow from the previous argument or statement", "A form of foreshadowing", "A character who contrasts with another character", "A type of logical fallacy based on circular reasoning"], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "In Latin, 'non sequitur' means 'it does not follow.' It's a statement that is grammatically correct but logically unconnected." },
        { "question": "What is the difference between a simile and a metaphor?", "answers": ["There is no difference", "A simile uses 'like' or 'as' to make a comparison, and a metaphor does not", "A metaphor uses 'like' or 'as' to make a comparison, and a simile does not", "A simile is an exaggeration"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "This is the key distinction. Simile: 'He is as strong as an ox.' Metaphor: 'He is an ox.'" },
        { "question": "Who wrote 'One Hundred Years of Solitude'?", "answers": ["Jorge Luis Borges", "Mario Vargas Llosa", "Gabriel García Márquez", "Isabel Allende"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Gabriel García Márquez, a Colombian novelist, won the Nobel Prize in Literature in 1982. 'One Hundred Years of Solitude' is his most famous work and a prime example of magical realism." },
        { "question": "What is 'stream of consciousness' as a narrative technique?", "answers": ["A narrative that follows a strict chronological order", "A character's thoughts and feelings are presented as they occur, in a continuous flow", "A story told from multiple perspectives", "A story told entirely through dialogue"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Stream of consciousness is a narrative mode that seeks to portray an individual's point of view by giving the written equivalent of the character's thought processes. James Joyce's 'Ulysses' is a famous example." }
      ]
    ]
  },
  "chemistry": {
    "easy": [
      [ // Set 1
        { "question": "What is the chemical symbol for water?", "answers": ["H2O", "CO2", "O2", "NaCl"], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "H2O represents two hydrogen atoms and one oxygen atom, which is the chemical composition of water." },
        { "question": "Which element has the chemical symbol 'O'?", "answers": ["Gold", "Oxygen", "Osmium", "Oxide"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "'O' is the chemical symbol for Oxygen, an element essential for life." },
        { "question": "What is the pH of a neutral substance like pure water?", "answers": ["0", "7", "14", "1"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "The pH scale ranges from 0 to 14. A pH of 7 is neutral, less than 7 is acidic, and greater than 7 is basic (alkaline)." },
        { "question": "What state of matter has a definite volume but no definite shape?", "answers": ["Solid", "Liquid", "Gas", "Plasma"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Liquids take the shape of their container but have a fixed volume." },
        { "question": "What is the chemical symbol for table salt?", "answers": ["H2SO4", "HCl", "NaCl", "C6H12O6"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Table salt is sodium chloride, with the chemical formula NaCl." },
        { "question": "Which of these is a noble gas?", "answers": ["Oxygen", "Hydrogen", "Helium", "Nitrogen"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Helium (He) is a noble gas, which means it is very stable and has a full outer electron shell." },
        { "question": "What is the process of a liquid turning into a gas called?", "answers": ["Melting", "Freezing", "Evaporation", "Condensation"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Evaporation is the phase transition from the liquid phase to the gas phase." },
        { "question": "What is the most abundant element in the Earth's atmosphere?", "answers": ["Oxygen", "Carbon", "Nitrogen", "Argon"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Nitrogen makes up about 78% of the Earth's atmosphere." },
        { "question": "Which particle has a positive charge in an atom?", "answers": ["Neutron", "Electron", "Proton", "Photon"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Protons are subatomic particles with a positive electric charge." },
        { "question": "What is the chemical symbol for Gold?", "answers": ["Go", "Gd", "Ag", "Au"], "correctAnswerIndex": 3, "explanation": "The chemical symbol for gold is 'Au', which comes from the Latin word for gold, 'aurum'." }
      ]
    ],
    "medium": [
      [ // Set 1
        { "question": "What is the difference between an atom and an ion?", "answers": ["An ion has a different number of neutrons", "An ion has an unequal number of protons and electrons", "An ion is always larger than an atom", "There is no difference"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "An ion is an atom or molecule that has gained or lost one or more of its valence electrons, giving it a net positive or negative charge." },
        { "question": "What type of chemical bond involves the sharing of electron pairs between atoms?", "answers": ["Ionic bond", "Covalent bond", "Metallic bond", "Hydrogen bond"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "A covalent bond is a chemical bond that involves the sharing of electron pairs between atoms." },
        { "question": "What is Avogadro's number?", "answers": ["The number of atoms in 12 grams of carbon-12", "The speed of light", "The charge of an electron", "The ideal gas constant"], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "Avogadro's number is approximately 6.022 x 10^23, and it represents the number of constituent particles (usually atoms or molecules) in one mole of a substance." },
        { "question": "What does the law of conservation of mass state?", "answers": ["Mass can be created but not destroyed", "Energy and mass are equivalent", "Mass is neither created nor destroyed in a chemical reaction", "The mass of a gas is proportional to its temperature"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "This law states that for any system closed to all transfers of matter and energy, the mass of the system must remain constant over time." },
        { "question": "What is an isotope?", "answers": ["An atom with a different number of protons", "An atom with a different number of electrons", "An atom with a different number of neutrons", "A charged atom"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Isotopes are variants of a particular chemical element which differ in neutron number, although all isotopes of a given element have the same number of protons." },
        { "question": "What is the general formula for an alkane?", "answers": ["C_n H_2n", "C_n H_2n+2", "C_n H_2n-2", "C_n H_n"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Alkanes are saturated hydrocarbons with the general formula C_n H_2n+2." },
        { "question": "What is an endothermic reaction?", "answers": ["A reaction that releases heat", "A reaction that absorbs heat from its surroundings", "A reaction that happens instantly", "A reaction that produces light"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "An endothermic reaction is a reaction in which the system absorbs energy from its surroundings in the form of heat." },
        { "question": "How do you calculate the molarity of a solution?", "answers": ["moles of solute / liters of solvent", "grams of solute / liters of solution", "moles of solute / liters of solution", "moles of solute / kilograms of solvent"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Molarity (M) is defined as the number of moles of solute per liter of solution." },
        { "question": "What is a catalyst?", "answers": ["A substance that is consumed in a reaction", "A substance that increases the rate of a chemical reaction without itself undergoing any permanent chemical change", "A substance that stops a reaction", "A substance that changes color during a reaction"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Catalysts work by providing an alternative reaction pathway with a lower activation energy." },
        { "question": "What is the name of the compound with the formula CH4?", "answers": ["Ethane", "Methane", "Propane", "Butane"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "CH4 is methane, the simplest alkane and the main component of natural gas." }
      ]
    ],
    "hard": [
      [ // Set 1
        { "question": "What is described by Schrödinger's wave equation?", "answers": ["The exact position of an electron", "The momentum of a particle", "The probability of finding an electron in a certain region of space", "The energy of a photon"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "The Schrödinger equation is a mathematical equation that describes the changes over time of a physical system in which quantum effects, such as wave–particle duality, are significant. It describes the electron as a wave function, and its square gives the probability density." },
        { "question": "What principle states that it is impossible to know simultaneously the exact position and momentum of a particle?", "answers": ["Aufbau Principle", "Pauli Exclusion Principle", "Hund's Rule", "Heisenberg Uncertainty Principle"], "correctAnswerIndex": 3, "explanation": "The Heisenberg Uncertainty Principle is a fundamental concept in quantum mechanics." },
        { "question": "What type of isomerism is exhibited by molecules that are non-superimposable mirror images of each other?", "answers": ["Structural isomerism", "Geometric isomerism", "Enantiomerism (Optical isomerism)", "Conformational isomerism"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Enantiomers are a pair of molecules that exist in two forms that are mirror images of one another but cannot be superimposed one upon the other. They are also known as chiral molecules." },
        { "question": "What is the Henderson-Hasselbalch equation used for?", "answers": ["To calculate the rate of a reaction", "To determine the enthalpy change of a reaction", "To calculate the pH of a buffer solution", "To find the equilibrium constant"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "The equation is pH = pKa + log([A-]/[HA]), where [A-] is the molar concentration of the conjugate base and [HA] is the molar concentration of the weak acid." },
        { "question": "In spectroscopy, what does NMR stand for?", "answers": ["New Molar Ratio", "Nuclear Magnetic Resonance", "Near-Molecule Radiation", "Newtonian Mass Reaction"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Nuclear Magnetic Resonance (NMR) spectroscopy is a technique used to determine the content and purity of a sample as well as its molecular structure." },
        { "question": "Which of the following describes a Diels-Alder reaction?", "answers": ["An elimination reaction", "A substitution reaction", "A cycloaddition reaction between a conjugated diene and a substituted alkene", "A rearrangement reaction"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "The Diels-Alder reaction is a powerful organic chemical reaction that forms a substituted cyclohexene ring. It is a key method for forming six-membered rings in organic synthesis." },
        { "question": "What is the role of a ligand in coordination chemistry?", "answers": ["It is the central metal atom", "It is an ion or molecule that binds to a central metal atom to form a coordination complex", "It is a solvent used to dissolve the complex", "It is a catalyst for complex formation"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "The bonding between metal and ligand generally involves formal donation of one or more of the ligand's electron pairs to the metal." },
        { "question": "What is the Gibbs free energy equation?", "answers": ["ΔG = ΔH - TΔS", "E = mc^2", "PV = nRT", "ΔH = ΔU + PΔV"], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "The Gibbs free energy (ΔG) of a system is a measure of the amount of usable energy in that system. ΔH is enthalpy, T is temperature, and ΔS is entropy." },
        { "question": "What is the mechanism of an SN2 reaction?", "answers": ["A two-step reaction with a carbocation intermediate", "A one-step reaction where bond-making and bond-breaking occur simultaneously", "A reaction involving a free-radical intermediate", "A reaction that only occurs in the presence of light"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "SN2 stands for bimolecular nucleophilic substitution. It is a concerted reaction, meaning it takes place in a single step." },
        { "question": "Which law relates the volume of a gas to its temperature at constant pressure?", "answers": ["Boyle's Law", "Charles's Law", "Gay-Lussac's Law", "Avogadro's Law"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Charles's Law (V/T = constant) states that the volume of a given mass of an ideal gas is directly proportional to its absolute temperature, assuming constant pressure." }
      ]
    ]
  },
  "biology": {
    "easy": [
      [ // Set 1
        { "question": "What is the powerhouse of the cell?", "answers": ["Nucleus", "Ribosome", "Mitochondrion", "Cell Wall"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "The mitochondrion generates most of the cell's supply of adenosine triphosphate (ATP), used as a source of chemical energy." },
        { "question": "What gas do plants absorb from the atmosphere for photosynthesis?", "answers": ["Oxygen", "Nitrogen", "Carbon Dioxide", "Hydrogen"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Plants use carbon dioxide, water, and sunlight to create their food (glucose) and release oxygen as a byproduct." },
        { "question": "Which of these is a primary producer in a food chain?", "answers": ["Lion", "Grass", "Rabbit", "Fungus"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Primary producers are organisms that create their own food from sunlight, like plants. Grass is a plant." },
        { "question": "How many chambers does the human heart have?", "answers": ["One", "Two", "Three", "Four"], "correctAnswerIndex": 3, "explanation": "The human heart has four chambers: two atria (upper chambers) and two ventricles (lower chambers)." },
        { "question": "What is the process by which plants make their own food called?", "answers": ["Respiration", "Transpiration", "Photosynthesis", "Germination"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Photosynthesis is the process used by plants, algae, and certain bacteria to harness energy from sunlight into chemical energy." },
        { "question": "What is the largest organ in the human body?", "answers": ["Liver", "Brain", "Skin", "Heart"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "The skin is the largest organ of the integumentary system, covering the entire outside of the body." },
        { "question": "Which part of the plant absorbs water and nutrients from the soil?", "answers": ["Leaf", "Stem", "Flower", "Root"], "correctAnswerIndex": 3, "explanation": "The roots anchor the plant and are the primary site of water and mineral absorption." },
        { "question": "What is the main function of the lungs?", "answers": ["Pumping blood", "Digesting food", "Breathing and gas exchange", "Filtering waste"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "The lungs are the primary organs of the respiratory system, where oxygen is taken into the body and carbon dioxide is expelled." },
        { "question": "What are the building blocks of proteins?", "answers": ["Sugars", "Fatty acids", "Amino acids", "Nucleotides"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Proteins are large biomolecules, or macromolecules, consisting of one or more long chains of amino acid residues." },
        { "question": "Which of these animals is a mammal?", "answers": ["Frog", "Shark", "Eagle", "Whale"], "correctAnswerIndex": 3, "explanation": "Whales are mammals; they are warm-blooded, breathe air, give birth to live young, and produce milk." }
      ]
    ],
    "medium": [
      [ // Set 1
        { "question": "What is the difference between DNA and RNA?", "answers": ["DNA is single-stranded, RNA is double-stranded", "DNA contains the sugar ribose, RNA contains deoxyribose", "DNA contains the base thymine, while RNA contains uracil in its place", "DNA is found in the cytoplasm, RNA is in the nucleus"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Both are nucleic acids, but they have key differences. One is that RNA uses uracil (U) instead of thymine (T)." },
        { "question": "What is meiosis?", "answers": ["Cell division that results in two identical daughter cells", "The process of a cell growing larger", "Cell division that results in four daughter cells each with half the number of chromosomes of the parent cell", "The process of building proteins"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Meiosis is a special type of cell division necessary for sexual reproduction in eukaryotes, creating gametes (sperm and egg cells)." },
        { "question": "What does a Punnett square predict?", "answers": ["The exact genetic makeup of an offspring", "The probability of an offspring having a particular genotype", "The rate of mutation", "The age of a fossil"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "A Punnett square is a diagram that is used to predict the genotypes of a particular cross or breeding experiment." },
        { "question": "What is the function of the ribosome in a cell?", "answers": ["Energy production", "Protein synthesis", "Waste disposal", "Storing genetic material"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Ribosomes are the cellular machinery responsible for making proteins by translating the information from messenger RNA (mRNA)." },
        { "question": "What is natural selection?", "answers": ["The process where humans choose which organisms reproduce", "The process whereby organisms better adapted to their environment tend to survive and produce more offspring", "The random change in the frequency of genes in a population", "The movement of genes from one population to another"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Proposed by Charles Darwin, natural selection is a key mechanism of evolution." },
        { "question": "What is the role of enzymes in the body?", "answers": ["They are a source of energy", "They store genetic information", "They act as catalysts to speed up chemical reactions", "They transport oxygen in the blood"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Enzymes are biological catalysts that significantly speed up the rate of virtually all of the chemical reactions that take place within cells." },
        { "question": "What is a 'genotype'?", "answers": ["The physical appearance of an organism", "The genetic makeup of an organism", "A section of DNA that codes for a protein", "A type of cell"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "An organism's genotype is its set of heritable genes that can be passed down from parents to offspring." },
        { "question": "What is the function of the circulatory system?", "answers": ["To break down food", "To send signals throughout the body", "To transport blood, nutrients, oxygen, and hormones to and from cells", "To provide structural support"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "The circulatory system, which includes the heart, blood vessels, and blood, is vital for fighting diseases and maintaining homeostasis." },
        { "question": "What is an ecosystem?", "answers": ["A group of organisms of the same species", "A community of living organisms in conjunction with the nonliving components of their environment, interacting as a system", "The natural home or environment of an organism", "The role an organism plays in its community"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Ecosystems can be of any size, from a small tide pool to a vast forest or ocean." },
        { "question": "What are homologous structures?", "answers": ["Structures that have the same function but different evolutionary origins", "Structures that are similar in related organisms because they were inherited from a common ancestor", "Structures that are reduced in size and have little or no function", "Structures that are only present in embryos"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "An example is the forelimb of a whale, a human, and a bat. They have different functions but a similar underlying bone structure, indicating a shared evolutionary past." }
      ]
    ],
    "hard": [
      [ // Set 1
        { "question": "What is the central dogma of molecular biology?", "answers": ["DNA -> Protein -> RNA", "RNA -> DNA -> Protein", "Protein -> RNA -> DNA", "DNA -> RNA -> Protein"], "correctAnswerIndex": 3, "explanation": "The central dogma, proposed by Francis Crick, describes the two-step process, transcription and translation, by which the information in genes flows into proteins: DNA → RNA → protein." },
        { "question": "What occurs during the process of transcription?", "answers": ["The cell divides", "A strand of RNA is synthesized from a DNA template", "Proteins are assembled on the ribosome", "DNA is replicated"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Transcription is the first step of gene expression, where a particular segment of DNA is copied into RNA (especially mRNA) by the enzyme RNA polymerase." },
        { "question": "What is the function of CRISPR-Cas9?", "answers": ["It is a type of virus", "It is a gene-editing technology that allows scientists to alter DNA sequences", "It is a protein that transports oxygen", "It is a method for cloning organisms"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "CRISPR-Cas9 is a powerful tool for editing genomes, allowing for the addition, removal, or alteration of particular DNA sequences." },
        { "question": "What is an action potential in a neuron?", "answers": ["The resting state of a neuron", "A short-lasting event in which the electrical membrane potential of a cell rapidly rises and falls", "The junction between two neurons", "A chemical that transmits signals across a synapse"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Action potentials are the fundamental units of communication in the nervous system, allowing signals to be transmitted quickly over long distances." },
        { "question": "What is the Krebs cycle (also known as the citric acid cycle)?", "answers": ["The process of breaking down glucose into pyruvate", "A series of chemical reactions used by all aerobic organisms to release stored energy through the oxidation of acetyl-CoA", "The process of converting light energy into chemical energy", "The process of synthesizing proteins"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "The Krebs cycle is a key part of cellular respiration, occurring in the mitochondrial matrix." },
        { "question": "What is allopatric speciation?", "answers": ["Speciation that occurs when two groups of the same species live in the same geographic location, but they evolve differently", "The formation of a new species in populations that are geographically isolated from one another", "The evolution of many diverse species from a common ancestor", "The process of a species going extinct"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Geographic isolation (e.g., by a mountain range or a river) can lead to divergence in the isolated populations, eventually resulting in the formation of new species." },
        { "question": "What is the function of the hormone insulin?", "answers": ["It increases blood sugar levels", "It regulates the sleep-wake cycle", "It stimulates growth", "It helps control blood sugar levels by signaling the liver, muscle, and fat cells to take in glucose from the blood"], "correctAnswerIndex": 3, "explanation": "Insulin is produced by the pancreas and is crucial for glucose metabolism. A lack of insulin or an inability to respond to it leads to diabetes." },
        { "question": "What is apoptosis?", "answers": ["Uncontrolled cell growth", "The process of programmed cell death", "The fusion of two cells", "The process of a cell becoming specialized"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Apoptosis is a normal and controlled part of an organism's growth or development, used to eliminate unwanted or damaged cells." },
        { "question": "Describe the lac operon.", "answers": ["A gene system that controls the production of proteins", "An operon required for the transport and metabolism of lactose in E. coli and some other enteric bacteria", "A set of genes responsible for antibiotic resistance", "A mechanism for DNA repair"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "The lac operon is a classic example of gene regulation in prokaryotes, allowing the cell to produce enzymes for lactose metabolism only when lactose is present." },
        { "question": "What is endosymbiotic theory?", "answers": ["The theory that life originated from non-living matter", "The theory that eukaryotic cells evolved from prokaryotic cells that engulfed other prokaryotic cells", "The theory of evolution by natural selection", "The theory that all living things are composed of cells"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "This theory proposes that organelles like mitochondria and chloroplasts were once free-living prokaryotic organisms that were taken inside another cell as an endosymbiont." }
      ]
    ]
  },
  "c": {
    "easy": [
      [ // Set 1
        { "question": "What is the correct way to declare an integer variable in C?", "answers": ["int x;", "integer x;", "x = int;", "declare x as int;"], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "In C, you declare an integer variable using the 'int' keyword followed by the variable name and a semicolon." },
        { "question": "Which function is the entry point of every C program?", "answers": ["start()", "begin()", "main()", "program()"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "The 'main()' function is where the execution of a C program begins." },
        { "question": "How do you print 'Hello, World!' to the console in C?", "answers": ["console.log('Hello, World!');", "print('Hello, World!');", "printf('Hello, World!');", "cout << 'Hello, World!';"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "The 'printf()' function from the <stdio.h> library is used for formatted output in C." },
        { "question": "What symbol is used for single-line comments in C?", "answers": ["#", "//", "/* */", "<!-- -->"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Single-line comments in C (and C++) start with '//'. The '/* */' syntax is used for multi-line comments." },
        { "question": "Which header file must be included to use the printf() function?", "answers": ["<stdlib.h>", "<math.h>", "<string.h>", "<stdio.h>"], "correctAnswerIndex": 3, "explanation": "'stdio.h' stands for Standard Input/Output, and it contains the declaration for the 'printf()' function." },
        { "question": "How do you terminate a statement in C?", "answers": ["With a period (.)", "With a comma (,)", "With a semicolon (;)", "With a colon (:)"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Every statement in C must end with a semicolon." },
        { "question": "What is the result of 10 % 3 in C?", "answers": ["0", "1", "2", "3"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "The modulo operator '%' gives the remainder of a division. 10 divided by 3 is 3 with a remainder of 1." },
        { "question": "Which loop is guaranteed to execute at least once?", "answers": ["for loop", "while loop", "do-while loop", "if statement"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "A do-while loop checks its condition at the end of the loop, so the body is always executed at least once." },
        { "question": "How do you declare a character array (string) in C?", "answers": ["string s = \"hello\";", "char s[] = \"hello\";", "String s = \"hello\";", "char s = \"hello\";"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "In C, strings are represented as arrays of characters, terminated by a null character '\\0'." },
        { "question": "What is the logical 'AND' operator in C?", "answers": ["&", "AND", "&&", "||"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "The '&&' operator is the logical AND. It returns true only if both operands are true." }
      ]
    ],
    "medium": [
      [ // Set 1
        { "question": "What is a pointer in C?", "answers": ["A variable that stores the value of another variable.", "A variable that stores the memory address of another variable.", "A special type of integer.", "A function that points to another function."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Pointers are a fundamental concept in C that allow for direct memory manipulation and dynamic memory allocation." },
        { "question": "How do you dynamically allocate memory for an array of 10 integers in C?", "answers": ["int* arr = new int[10];", "int* arr = malloc(10 * sizeof(int));", "int arr[10];", "int* arr = alloc(10, int);"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "The 'malloc' function from <stdlib.h> is used for dynamic memory allocation. 'sizeof(int)' ensures the correct number of bytes is allocated." },
        { "question": "What is the difference between '==' and '=' in C?", "answers": ["'==' is for assignment, '=' is for comparison.", "There is no difference.", "'=' is for assignment, '==' is for comparison.", "'=' is for initialization, '==' is for assignment."], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "A single equals sign '=' is the assignment operator. A double equals sign '==' is the equality comparison operator." },
        { "question": "What is a 'struct' in C?", "answers": ["A built-in data type for strings.", "A collection of variables of the same type.", "A user-defined data type that groups together variables of different data types.", "A type of loop."], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Structs allow you to create complex data types by bundling different variables under a single name." },
        { "question": "What does the 'break' statement do in a loop?", "answers": ["Skips the current iteration and continues with the next.", "Terminates the loop immediately.", "Pauses the execution of the loop.", "Restarts the loop from the beginning."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "The 'break' statement is used to exit a loop (for, while, do-while) or a switch statement prematurely." },
        { "question": "How do you pass a variable by reference to a function in C?", "answers": ["By passing the variable directly.", "By passing a pointer to the variable.", "By using the '&' symbol in the function definition.", "C does not support pass-by-reference."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "C is strictly pass-by-value. To simulate pass-by-reference and allow a function to modify a variable, you must pass a pointer to that variable." },
        { "question": "What is recursion?", "answers": ["A loop that never ends.", "A function that calls itself.", "A way to sort data.", "A type of data structure."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Recursion is a programming technique where a function calls itself to solve a problem. It must have a base case to stop the recursion." },
        { "question": "What is the purpose of the 'typedef' keyword?", "answers": ["To define a new function.", "To declare a global variable.", "To create a new name (alias) for an existing data type.", "To define a macro."], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "'typedef' is used to give a new, often simpler or more descriptive, name to a data type. For example, `typedef unsigned char BYTE;`" },
        { "question": "What will `sizeof(char)` return?", "answers": ["0", "1", "2", "4"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "The C standard guarantees that `sizeof(char)` will always be 1, as it is the basic unit of memory measurement in C." },
        { "question": "Which operator is used to access the value at a memory address stored in a pointer?", "answers": ["& (address-of operator)", "* (dereference operator)", "-> (arrow operator)", ". (dot operator)"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "The dereference or indirection operator (*) is used to get the value stored at the address pointed to by the pointer." }
      ]
    ],
    "hard": [
      [ // Set 1
        { "question": "What is a 'dangling pointer'?", "answers": ["A pointer that has not been initialized.", "A pointer that points to a memory location that has been deallocated (freed).", "A pointer that points to the address 0 (NULL).", "A pointer to a pointer."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Accessing a dangling pointer leads to undefined behavior, which can cause crashes or subtle bugs, as the memory it points to may have been reallocated for another purpose." },
        { "question": "What is the difference between `malloc()` and `calloc()`?", "answers": ["`malloc()` allocates memory, `calloc()` frees it.", "`calloc()` allocates memory and initializes all bits to zero, while `malloc()` leaves the memory uninitialized.", "`malloc()` is for arrays, `calloc()` is for single variables.", "There is no difference in their function, only in their naming."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "`calloc()` (contiguous allocation) also takes two arguments (number of elements, size of each element), while `malloc()` takes a single argument (total bytes)." },
        { "question": "What are function pointers?", "answers": ["Pointers that point to the first instruction of a function in memory.", "Functions that return a pointer.", "A syntax error.", "Pointers used exclusively inside functions."], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "Function pointers allow you to treat functions like data, meaning you can pass functions as arguments to other functions, or store them in arrays, which is useful for implementing callbacks or strategy patterns." },
        { "question": "What does the `volatile` keyword signify?", "answers": ["The variable cannot be modified.", "The variable is stored in a special memory region.", "The variable's value can be changed at any time by something outside the program's control (e.g., hardware, another thread).", "The variable is a constant."], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "The `volatile` keyword tells the compiler not to optimize away reads or writes to this variable, because its value might change unexpectedly. It's crucial for embedded systems and multi-threaded programming." },
        { "question": "What is a 'union' in C?", "answers": ["A struct where all members share the same memory location.", "Another name for a struct.", "A way to combine two source files.", "A special type of pointer."], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "A union can hold only one of its members at a time. The size of the union is the size of its largest member. It's used for memory saving and interpreting a piece of memory in different ways." },
        { "question": "Explain the C preprocessor.", "answers": ["It's the part of the compiler that generates machine code.", "It's a tool for debugging C code.", "It's a program that processes the source code before it passes to the compiler, handling directives like #include, #define, and #if.", "It's the linker that combines object files."], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "The preprocessor modifies the source code based on directives. For example, `#include <stdio.h>` physically pastes the content of the `stdio.h` file into your source code." },
        { "question": "What is the purpose of the `static` keyword when applied to a local variable?", "answers": ["It makes the variable global.", "It makes the variable constant.", "It makes the variable's lifetime extend across the entire run of the program, instead of being created and destroyed each time the function is entered and exited.", "It's a syntax error."], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "A static local variable retains its value between function calls. It is initialized only once." },
        { "question": "What's the difference between `#include <file.h>` and `#include \"file.h\"`?", "answers": ["There is no difference.", "<file.h> is for C++ headers, \"file.h\" is for C headers.", "<file.h> searches system directories first, while \"file.h\" searches the current directory first.", "\"file.h\" searches system directories first, while <file.h> searches the current directory first."], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "You use angle brackets for standard library headers and double quotes for your own project's headers." },
        { "question": "What are bit fields in a C struct?", "answers": ["A way to specify the number of bits a member should occupy.", "A field that can only be a pointer.", "A field that must be an integer.", "A struct that can only contain boolean flags."], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "Bit fields allow for packing data tightly, specifying that a member should only use a certain number of bits. This is very useful in low-level programming where memory is at a premium. Example: `unsigned int isActive : 1;`" },
        { "question": "What does the `const` qualifier mean when applied to a pointer declaration like `const int *p;`?", "answers": ["The pointer `p` is constant and cannot be changed to point to another integer.", "The integer value that `p` points to is constant and cannot be changed through this pointer.", "Both the pointer and the integer it points to are constant.", "It is a syntax error."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "`const int *p` (or `int const *p`) is a pointer to a constant integer. You can change `p` to point to something else, but you cannot change the value of the integer it points to using `*p`." }
      ]
    ]
  },
  "c++": {
    "easy": [
      [ // Set 1
        { "question": "What is the main difference between C and C++?", "answers": ["C++ is a scripting language, C is not.", "C++ supports object-oriented programming (OOP), while C does not.", "C++ uses a different syntax for loops.", "There is no significant difference."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "C++ was built upon C and introduced features like classes, inheritance, and polymorphism, which are core concepts of OOP." },
        { "question": "How do you print 'Hello, World!' to the console in C++?", "answers": ["printf('Hello, World!');", "System.out.println('Hello, World!');", "cout << \"Hello, World!\";", "print 'Hello, World!'"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "In C++, the 'cout' object, used with the stream insertion operator '<<', is the standard way to output text to the console. It's part of the iostream library." },
        { "question": "Which keyword is used to define a class in C++?", "answers": ["struct", "object", "class", "type"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "The 'class' keyword is used to declare a new user-defined type that can contain data members and member functions." },
        { "question": "What is an object in C++?", "answers": ["A blueprint for creating variables.", "Another name for a function.", "An instance of a class.", "A keyword for memory allocation."], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "A class is like a blueprint, and an object is the actual house built from that blueprint. It's a concrete entity created from a class." },
        { "question": "How do you start a single-line comment in C++?", "answers": ["#", "//", "/* */", "--"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "C++ uses '//' for single-line comments, just like C. It also supports '/* */' for multi-line comments." },
        { "question": "What is the purpose of a constructor?", "answers": ["To destroy an object.", "To initialize the data members of an object when it is created.", "To perform a mathematical calculation.", "To define the main logic of the program."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "A constructor is a special member function that is automatically called when an object of a class is created." },
        { "question": "Which header file is needed for using `cout` and `cin`?", "answers": ["<stdio.h>", "<string>", "<iostream>", "<stdlib>"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "`iostream` stands for input-output stream and contains the definitions for objects like `cin` (standard input) and `cout` (standard output)." },
        { "question": "What does the `new` keyword do in C++?", "answers": ["It creates a new file.", "It starts a new thread.", "It dynamically allocates memory for an object.", "It defines a new namespace."], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "The `new` operator allocates memory from the free store (heap) for an object and returns a pointer to it." },
        { "question": "In C++, how are strings commonly handled?", "answers": ["Using character arrays as in C.", "Using the `std::string` class.", "Using the `String` keyword.", "Using a linked list of characters."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "The C++ Standard Library provides a powerful `std::string` class that handles memory management and provides many useful string manipulation functions, making it safer and easier than C-style character arrays." },
        { "question": "What is the scope resolution operator?", "answers": [":", "->", ".", "::"], "correctAnswerIndex": 3, "explanation": "The scope resolution operator `::` is used to define a member function outside a class, or to access a class's static members or a global variable when a local variable has the same name." }
      ]
    ],
    "medium": [
      [ // Set 1
        { "question": "What is inheritance in C++?", "answers": ["The ability of a class to derive properties and characteristics from another class.", "A mechanism to create multiple objects from a single class.", "The process of hiding implementation details from the user.", "A way to combine data and functions into a single unit."], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "Inheritance allows for creating a new class (derived class) from an existing class (base class), promoting code reuse and establishing an 'is-a' relationship." },
        { "question": "What is polymorphism?", "answers": ["A class having many forms or methods with the same name but different parameters.", "The process of creating objects.", "Hiding data within a class.", "The ability for an object to be inherited by another class."], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "Polymorphism, meaning 'many forms', allows objects of different classes to be treated as objects of a common base class. It's often implemented using virtual functions." },
        { "question": "What is the difference between `public`, `private`, and `protected` access specifiers?", "answers": ["They are all the same.", "`public` members are accessible from anywhere, `private` only within the class, `protected` within the class and its derived classes.", "`private` members are accessible from anywhere, `public` only within the class.", "`protected` members can only be accessed by friend functions."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "These access specifiers control the visibility and accessibility of class members, which is a key part of encapsulation." },
        { "question": "What is a virtual function?", "answers": ["A function that cannot be overridden.", "A member function that is declared within a base class and is re-defined by a derived class.", "A function that exists only in theory.", "A global function that can be called from any class."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Virtual functions are the mechanism that enables dynamic polymorphism (late binding). When you call a virtual function through a base class pointer, the version in the derived class is executed." },
        { "question": "What is the purpose of a destructor?", "answers": ["To initialize an object.", "To create a copy of an object.", "A special member function that is called when an object goes out of scope or is explicitly deleted.", "To allocate memory for an object."], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Destructors are used to deallocate memory and do other cleanup for a class object and its class members when the object is destroyed." },
        { "question": "What is function overloading?", "answers": ["Defining multiple functions with the same name but different parameters.", "A function that calls itself.", "Overriding a function in a derived class.", "A function that is too complex."], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "Function overloading allows you to have multiple functions with the same name as long as their parameter lists are different in number or type. This is a form of static polymorphism." },
        { "question": "What is a reference in C++?", "answers": ["Another name for a pointer.", "An alias or an alternative name for an already existing variable.", "A variable that stores a memory address.", "A read-only variable."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "A reference must be initialized when it is created and cannot be changed to refer to another variable later. It provides a way to pass arguments to functions by reference." },
        { "question": "What does the 'const' keyword do when applied to a member function (e.g., `void func() const;`)?", "answers": ["It indicates that the function returns a constant value.", "It indicates that the function cannot be called.", "It indicates that the function will not modify the state (data members) of the object.", "It makes the function static."], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "A const member function is a promise that it will not change the object's data. This allows the function to be called on const objects." },
        { "question": "What is the Standard Template Library (STL)?", "answers": ["A library for creating graphical user interfaces.", "A set of C++ template classes to provide common programming data structures and functions.", "A library for network programming.", "A tool for debugging C++ code."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "The STL provides a collection of containers (like vector, list, map), iterators to step through them, and algorithms (like sort, find) that operate on them." },
        { "question": "What is the difference between a `struct` and a `class` in C++?", "answers": ["`struct` members are `public` by default, while `class` members are `private` by default.", "`class` cannot have member functions, but `struct` can.", "`struct` cannot be used for inheritance.", "There is no difference."], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "Functionally, they are almost identical. The only difference is the default access level for their members." }
      ]
    ],
    "hard": [
      [ // Set 1
        { "question": "What is RAII (Resource Acquisition Is Initialization)?", "answers": ["A design pattern for error handling.", "A programming idiom where resource management is tied to object lifetime.", "A memory allocation technique.", "A type of template metaprogramming."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "In RAII, you acquire a resource in an object's constructor and release it in the destructor. This ensures resources (like memory, file handles, or network sockets) are automatically cleaned up when the object goes out of scope, preventing leaks." },
        { "question": "What is a 'smart pointer'?", "answers": ["A pointer that automatically converts between types.", "A pointer that manages the memory it points to, automatically deallocating it when it's no longer needed.", "A pointer that can point to member functions.", "A pointer that is faster than a regular pointer."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Smart pointers like `std::unique_ptr` and `std::shared_ptr` are wrappers around raw pointers that automate memory management, helping to prevent memory leaks and dangling pointers." },
        { "question": "What is the difference between `std::vector` and `std::list`?", "answers": ["`vector` is a linked list, `list` is an array.", "`vector` stores elements in contiguous memory, while `list` is a doubly-linked list.", "`list` is faster for random access.", "`vector` cannot be resized."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "`std::vector` provides fast random access but slow insertion/deletion in the middle. `std::list` provides fast insertion/deletion anywhere but slow random access (requires traversal)." },
        { "question": "What is template metaprogramming (TMP)?", "answers": ["A way to program graphics cards.", "A technique where the C++ compiler is used to generate code at compile time.", "A method for runtime polymorphism.", "A style of object-oriented design."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "TMP uses templates to perform computations during compilation. The result of these computations can be types, constants, or functions, allowing for powerful compile-time optimizations and code generation." },
        { "question": "What is the 'Rule of Three/Five/Zero'?", "answers": ["A guideline on when to declare custom copy/move constructors, assignment operators, and a destructor.", "A rule about the maximum number of inheritance levels.", "A naming convention for C++ classes.", "A set of performance optimization rules."], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "If a class needs a user-defined destructor, copy constructor, or copy assignment operator (Rule of Three), it likely needs all three. With C++11, this extends to move constructors and move assignment operators (Rule of Five). The Rule of Zero suggests designing classes to not need any of them by using standard library containers." },
        { "question": "What is perfect forwarding?", "answers": ["A mechanism that allows a function template to pass its arguments to another function while preserving their value categories (lvalue/rvalue).", "A way to guarantee that a function will be inlined.", "A feature for exception handling.", "A method for multi-threaded programming."], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "Perfect forwarding is achieved using forwarding references (T&&) and `std::forward`. It's crucial for writing generic factory functions and wrappers that don't interfere with move semantics." },
        { "question": "What is SFINAE (Substitution Failure Is Not An Error)?", "answers": ["A principle that allows a compiler to discard invalid template specializations without causing a compile error.", "A type of runtime error.", "A memory leak detection tool.", "A C++ coding standard."], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "SFINAE is a key principle that enables template metaprogramming techniques like `std::enable_if`. If a substitution of template parameters into a function signature is invalid, the compiler just ignores that overload instead of stopping with an error." },
        { "question": "What is the purpose of the `explicit` keyword?", "answers": ["To make a function's implementation visible in the header file.", "To prevent the compiler from performing implicit type conversions for a constructor or conversion operator.", "To declare a function as thread-safe.", "To force a function to be inlined."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "By marking a single-argument constructor as `explicit`, you prevent the compiler from using it for unintentional conversions, which can make code safer and less surprising. For example, `explicit MyClass(int x);` prevents `MyClass obj = 5;` from compiling." },
        { "question": "What is name lookup and Argument-Dependent Lookup (ADL)?", "answers": ["The process of linking a C++ program.", "The process the compiler uses to find the declaration for a name (variable, function, etc.).", "A debugging technique.", "A way to handle exceptions."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Name lookup has complex rules. ADL (also called Koenig lookup) is a special rule where the compiler also looks for function names in the namespaces of the function's arguments." },
        { "question": "What is the Curiously Recurring Template Pattern (CRTP)?", "answers": ["An idiom where a class X derives from a template class instantiated with X itself (e.g., `class X : public Base<X>`).", "A recursive function template.", "A design pattern for creating singletons.", "A common mistake in C++ template programming."], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "CRTP is a form of static polymorphism. It allows the base class template to use the derived class's type to call its members without virtual functions, avoiding the overhead of dynamic dispatch." }
      ]
    ]
  },
  "java": {
    "easy": [
      [ // Set 1
        { "question": "Which keyword is used to define a class in Java?", "answers": ["class", "type", "struct", "object"], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "The 'class' keyword is used to declare a new class, which serves as a blueprint for creating objects." },
        { "question": "What is the entry point for any Java application?", "answers": ["start()", "run()", "main()", "execute()"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "The Java Virtual Machine (JVM) starts execution by looking for a method with the signature 'public static void main(String[] args)'." },
        { "question": "How do you print 'Hello, World!' to the console in Java?", "answers": ["printf('Hello, World!');", "cout << \"Hello, World!\";", "System.out.println(\"Hello, World!\");", "console.log('Hello, World!');"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "'System.out' is the standard output stream, and 'println' is a method to print a line of text." },
        { "question": "Which of these is NOT a primitive data type in Java?", "answers": ["int", "float", "String", "boolean"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "'String' in Java is an object (an instance of the String class), not a primitive type. int, float, and boolean are primitives." },
        { "question": "How do you declare a variable that will hold an integer value in Java?", "answers": ["integer x;", "int x;", "x = int;", "num x;"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "The 'int' keyword is used to declare variables that will store 32-bit signed integer values." },
        { "question": "What is the file extension for a compiled Java class file?", "answers": [".java", ".jar", ".class", ".exe"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "The Java compiler ('javac') compiles a '.java' source file into a '.class' file containing Java bytecode." },
        { "question": "How do you create an object (instance) of a class named 'Car'?", "answers": ["Car myCar = create Car();", "Car myCar = Car();", "Car myCar = new Car();", "new Car() -> myCar;"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "The 'new' keyword is used to allocate memory and create a new instance of a class." },
        { "question": "Which loop is guaranteed to execute at least once?", "answers": ["for", "while", "do-while", "enhanced for"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "A 'do-while' loop evaluates its condition at the end of the loop's body, ensuring the body is executed at least one time." },
        { "question": "What symbol is used for single-line comments in Java?", "answers": ["#", "--", "/* */", "//"], "correctAnswerIndex": 3, "explanation": "Java uses '//' for single-line comments and '/* */' for multi-line comments, similar to C++ and C#." },
        { "question": "What does the 'null' keyword represent in Java?", "answers": ["The number zero.", "An empty string.", "A reference that does not point to any object.", "A syntax error."], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "'null' is a literal for a reference type, representing the absence of an object." }
      ]
    ],
    "medium": [
      [ // Set 1
        { "question": "What is the difference between an 'interface' and an 'abstract class' in Java?", "answers": ["An interface can have method implementations, but an abstract class cannot.", "A class can implement multiple interfaces but can only extend one abstract class.", "An abstract class cannot have constructors.", "There is no difference."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "This is a key difference. Java does not support multiple inheritance for classes, but it allows a class to implement any number of interfaces." },
        { "question": "What is method overloading?", "answers": ["Defining a method in a subclass that is already defined in the parent class.", "Defining multiple methods in the same class with the same name but different parameter lists.", "A method that calls itself.", "A method that is too long."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "The compiler determines which version of the method to call based on the arguments provided. This is a form of static polymorphism." },
        { "question": "What is method overriding?", "answers": ["Providing a specific implementation for a method in a subclass that is already defined in its superclass.", "Defining multiple methods with the same name.", "Changing the return type of a method.", "Making a method final."], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "Method overriding is a key feature of polymorphism in Java, allowing a child class to provide its own version of a method from the parent class." },
        { "question": "What is the purpose of the 'super' keyword?", "answers": ["To refer to the current object instance.", "To call a method in a different class.", "To refer to the immediate parent class object.", "To declare a static variable."], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "'super' is used to call parent class constructors (`super()`) or to call parent class methods (`super.methodName()`)." },
        { "question": "What are the `public`, `private`, `protected`, and default access modifiers?", "answers": ["They control the visibility of classes, methods, and variables.", "They define the data type of a variable.", "They are used for exception handling.", "They control the flow of a program."], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "`public` is accessible from anywhere. `private` is only accessible within the same class. `protected` is accessible within the same package and by subclasses. Default (no modifier) is accessible only within the same package." },
        { "question": "What is the Java Virtual Machine (JVM)?", "answers": ["A text editor for writing Java code.", "The Java compiler.", "An abstract computing machine that enables a computer to run a Java program.", "A library of Java classes."], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "The JVM is a crucial component of the Java platform. It interprets compiled Java bytecode for a computer's processor, making Java 'write once, run anywhere'." },
        { "question": "What is the difference between '==' and the '.equals()' method for Strings?", "answers": ["There is no difference.", "'==' compares the object references, while '.equals()' compares the actual content of the strings.", "'.equals()' compares the object references, while '==' compares the string content.", "'==' is faster than '.equals()'."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "When comparing strings for equality of their content, you should always use the `.equals()` method. `==` only checks if two references point to the exact same object in memory." },
        { "question": "What is a 'constructor' in Java?", "answers": ["A method used to destroy an object.", "A special method used to initialize a newly created object.", "A method that returns a value.", "A method to copy an object."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "A constructor is called when an object of a class is created. It can be used to set initial values for object attributes." },
        { "question": "What is garbage collection?", "answers": ["The process of manually freeing memory.", "A form of automatic memory management where the JVM reclaims memory occupied by objects that are no longer in use.", "The process of clearing the console.", "A feature for deleting files."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Garbage collection is a key feature of Java that helps prevent memory leaks by automatically managing memory deallocation." },
        { "question": "What is the purpose of the `static` keyword in Java?", "answers": ["It indicates that a variable or method belongs to the class itself, rather than to any one object.", "It makes a variable a constant.", "It makes a method run in a separate thread.", "It specifies that a variable can only hold text."], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "Static members are shared among all instances of a class. You can access them using the class name, without creating an object." }
      ]
    ],
    "hard": [
      [ // Set 1
        { "question": "What is the difference between `String`, `StringBuilder`, and `StringBuffer`?", "answers": ["They are all the same.", "`String` is immutable, while `StringBuilder` and `StringBuffer` are mutable. `StringBuffer` is thread-safe, `StringBuilder` is not.", "`String` is mutable, while the others are not.", "`StringBuilder` is used for numbers, `String` for text."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Because `String` objects are immutable, creating a new string for every modification is inefficient. `StringBuilder` is recommended for single-threaded string manipulation, while `StringBuffer` is used in multi-threaded environments." },
        { "question": "Explain the Java Memory Model (JMM).", "answers": ["It is the specification that describes how threads interact through memory.", "It defines the layout of a class file.", "It is the algorithm used by the garbage collector.", "It describes how the JVM is implemented."], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "The JMM defines the happens-before relationship and rules for visibility of shared variables between threads, ensuring that multithreaded programs behave predictably across different hardware architectures." },
        { "question": "What are Generics in Java?", "answers": ["A way to automatically generate code.", "A feature that provides compile-time type safety for collections and classes.", "A type of exception.", "A framework for building user interfaces."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Generics allow you to create classes, interfaces, and methods that operate on types as parameters. For example, `List<String>` ensures that the list can only hold String objects, preventing ClassCastExceptions at runtime." },
        { "question": "What is the difference between a checked and an unchecked exception?", "answers": ["Checked exceptions are errors, unchecked exceptions are not.", "Checked exceptions must be declared or handled in a try-catch block; unchecked exceptions do not have this requirement.", "Unchecked exceptions must be handled, while checked exceptions can be ignored.", "There is no difference."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Checked exceptions (subclasses of Exception, but not RuntimeException) represent recoverable conditions that a well-written application should anticipate and recover from. Unchecked exceptions (subclasses of RuntimeException) represent bugs or logic errors in the code." },
        { "question": "What is reflection in Java?", "answers": ["The ability of a program to examine and modify its own structure and behavior at runtime.", "A technique for creating mirror images of objects.", "A method for improving performance.", "A security feature of the JVM."], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "The Reflection API allows you to inspect classes, interfaces, fields, and methods at runtime, and even instantiate objects and invoke methods, without knowing their names at compile time." },
        { "question": "What is the `transient` keyword used for?", "answers": ["To mark a variable as temporary.", "To indicate that a field should not be serialized when an object is written to a stream.", "To make a variable thread-safe.", "To create a constant variable."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "When an object is serialized (converted to a byte stream), the values of its transient fields are ignored. This is useful for fields that are either security-sensitive or can be recalculated." },
        { "question": "What is a 'lambda expression' in Java?", "answers": ["A mathematical formula.", "An anonymous function that can be treated as a value.", "A new type of loop.", "A way to define a class."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Introduced in Java 8, lambda expressions provide a clear and concise way to represent a method interface using an expression. They are often used to implement functional interfaces (interfaces with a single abstract method)." },
        { "question": "What is the Stream API?", "answers": ["An API for reading and writing files.", "An API introduced in Java 8 that provides a way to process sequences of elements in a functional style.", "An API for network communication.", "An API for creating graphical user interfaces."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "The Stream API allows for powerful, declarative operations on collections, such as `filter`, `map`, and `reduce`, which can be chained together to form a processing pipeline." },
        { "question": "What is the difference between `hashCode()` and `equals()`?", "answers": ["They are used for the same purpose.", "If two objects are equal according to `equals()`, they must have the same hash code. The reverse is not necessarily true.", "If two objects have the same hash code, they must be equal.", "`hashCode()` is used for sorting, `equals()` for comparison."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "This is the fundamental contract between `hashCode()` and `equals()`. Hash-based collections like `HashMap` and `HashSet` rely on this contract to function correctly. Unequal objects can have the same hash code (a 'collision'), but equal objects MUST have the same hash code." },
        { "question": "What is the 'volatile' keyword in Java?", "answers": ["It marks a variable as unable to be changed.", "It ensures that a variable is stored only in main memory, not in CPU caches.", "It indicates a variable is temporary.", "It is used for serialization."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "The `volatile` keyword guarantees that any read of a volatile variable will see the most recent write by any thread, ensuring visibility of changes across threads. It is a weaker form of synchronization than a `synchronized` block." }
      ]
    ]
  },
  "javascript": {
    "easy": [
      [ // Set 1
        { "question": "How do you declare a variable in JavaScript that can be reassigned?", "answers": ["const myVar = 10;", "let myVar = 10;", "var myVar = 10;", "Both 'let' and 'var'"], "correctAnswerIndex": 3, "explanation": "'var' is the older way, while 'let' (introduced in ES6) has block scope and is generally preferred. Both can be reassigned." },
        { "question": "What is the result of `\"5\" + 3` in JavaScript?", "answers": ["8", "\"53\"", "35", "Error"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "JavaScript performs type coercion. The '+' operator, when used with a string, performs concatenation, so the number 3 is converted to a string '3'." },
        { "question": "How do you write 'Hello, World!' to the browser's console?", "answers": ["System.out.println('Hello, World!');", "print('Hello, World!');", "console.log('Hello, World!');", "document.write('Hello, World!');"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "The 'console.log()' method is the standard way to output information for debugging purposes in web development." },
        { "question": "Which of these is NOT a JavaScript data type?", "answers": ["String", "Number", "Boolean", "Character"], "correctAnswerIndex": 3, "explanation": "JavaScript does not have a separate 'Character' type. Single characters are handled as strings of length 1." },
        { "question": "What does the `===` operator do?", "answers": ["It performs an assignment.", "It checks for equality of value, allowing for type coercion.", "It checks for strict equality, without type coercion (both value and type must match).", "It checks if a value is greater than or equal to another."], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Strict equality (`===`) is generally preferred over loose equality (`==`) to avoid unexpected results from type coercion." },
        { "question": "How do you define a function in JavaScript?", "answers": ["def myFunction() {}", "function myFunction() {}", "void myFunction() {}", "method myFunction() {}"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "You can define a function using the 'function' keyword, followed by the function name, parentheses for parameters, and curly braces for the function body." },
        { "question": "How do you create an array in JavaScript?", "answers": ["let colors = {\"red\", \"green\", \"blue\"};", "let colors = [\"red\", \"green\", \"blue\"];", "let colors = array(\"red\", \"green\", \"blue\");", "let colors = <\"red\", \"green\", \"blue\">;"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Arrays are created using square brackets `[]`, with elements separated by commas." },
        { "question": "What method would you use to add a new item to the end of an array?", "answers": ["array.add()", "array.append()", "array.push()", "array.insert()"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "The `push()` method adds one or more elements to the end of an array and returns the new length of the array." },
        { "question": "How do you start a single-line comment in JavaScript?", "answers": ["#", "//", "<!--", "/*"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "JavaScript uses '//' for single-line comments and '/* */' for multi-line comments." },
        { "question": "What does `NaN` stand for?", "answers": ["No Available Number", "Not a Name", "Null and Negative", "Not a Number"], "correctAnswerIndex": 3, "explanation": "`NaN` is a property of the global object. It is a value representing that a value is not a legal number, often the result of an invalid mathematical operation like `0/0`." }
      ]
    ],
    "medium": [
      [ // Set 1
        { "question": "What is a 'closure' in JavaScript?", "answers": ["A way to close a browser window.", "A function that has access to its own scope, the scope of the outer function, and the global scope.", "A syntax error.", "A built-in method for arrays."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "A closure is created when a function is defined inside another function, allowing the inner function to access the outer function's variables long after the outer function has finished executing." },
        { "question": "What is the difference between `let`, `const`, and `var`?", "answers": ["There is no difference.", "`var` is function-scoped; `let` and `const` are block-scoped. `const` cannot be reassigned.", "`const` is function-scoped; `let` and `var` are block-scoped.", "`var` and `let` can be reassigned, `const` cannot."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Understanding scope is crucial in JavaScript. `let` and `const` were introduced in ES6 to provide more predictable, block-level scoping compared to the older, function-scoped `var`." },
        { "question": "What does 'event bubbling' mean?", "answers": ["An error that crashes the browser.", "The order in which event handlers are called when one element is nested inside another, from the innermost element outward.", "A CSS animation effect.", "A memory leak in a JavaScript application."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "When an event happens on an element, it first runs the handlers on it, then on its parent, then all the way up on other ancestors. This is the 'bubbling' phase." },
        { "question": "What is a 'Promise' in JavaScript?", "answers": ["A guarantee that a function will not have errors.", "An object representing the eventual completion (or failure) of an asynchronous operation and its resulting value.", "A syntax for declaring variables.", "A way to schedule a function to run at a later time."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Promises are fundamental to modern asynchronous JavaScript, providing a cleaner alternative to callback functions for handling operations like network requests." },
        { "question": "What is the purpose of the `this` keyword?", "answers": ["It refers to the current HTML document.", "It refers to the object from which a function was called.", "It is a reference to the previously executed function.", "It refers to the global window object."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "The value of `this` is determined by how a function is called. Its behavior can be confusing, especially with arrow functions, which lexically bind `this`." },
        { "question": "What is the difference between `null` and `undefined`?", "answers": ["They are exactly the same.", "`undefined` means a variable has been declared but not assigned a value, while `null` is an assignment value representing no value.", "`null` is a number, `undefined` is an object.", "`undefined` is an error, `null` is not."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "You can think of `undefined` as an unintentional absence of value, and `null` as an intentional absence of value." },
        { "question": "What are arrow functions (`=>`)?", "answers": ["A shorter syntax for writing function expressions; they do not have their own `this`, `arguments`, `super`, or `new.target`.", "A way to draw arrows on an HTML canvas.", "A special type of loop.", "A feature for creating CSS animations."], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "Arrow functions are syntactically more compact and have a different behavior for the `this` keyword, which they inherit from the surrounding (lexical) scope." },
        { "question": "What is the DOM?", "answers": ["A JavaScript library for animations.", "The Document Object Model: a programming interface for web documents.", "A data storage system in the browser.", "The JavaScript engine used by Google Chrome."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "The DOM represents the page so that programs can change the document structure, style, and content. JavaScript is the primary language used to manipulate the DOM." },
        { "question": "What is JSON?", "answers": ["A JavaScript function.", "JavaScript Object Notation: a lightweight data-interchange format.", "A type of JavaScript compiler.", "A method for creating user interfaces."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "JSON is easy for humans to read and write and easy for machines to parse and generate. It is often used for serializing and transmitting structured data over a network connection." },
        { "question": "What is the purpose of `async/await`?", "answers": ["To make functions run faster.", "Syntactic sugar built on top of Promises that makes asynchronous code look and behave more like synchronous code.", "A way to declare variables.", "A method for handling CSS styles."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "`async` functions always return a Promise, and the `await` keyword pauses the function execution until the Promise is settled (resolved or rejected)." }
      ]
    ],
    "hard": [
      [ // Set 1
        { "question": "What is 'hoisting' in JavaScript?", "answers": ["A way to lift elements visually on a webpage.", "A mechanism where variable and function declarations are moved to the top of their containing scope before code execution.", "A security vulnerability.", "An error that occurs when a variable is used before it's declared."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Hoisting means you can use a variable declared with `var` or a function declaration before it appears in the code. However, only the declaration is hoisted, not the initialization. `let` and `const` are also hoisted but are not initialized, leading to a 'Temporal Dead Zone'." },
        { "question": "What are JavaScript Prototypes?", "answers": ["A built-in object that simplifies common tasks.", "An internal property of an object, which is a reference to another object, used to implement inheritance.", "A first version of a new JavaScript library.", "A feature for creating private members in a class."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Every object in JavaScript has a prototype. When trying to access a property of an object, if the property is not found on the object itself, the JavaScript engine looks at the object's prototype, then the prototype's prototype, and so on, creating the 'prototype chain'." },
        { "question": "What is the Event Loop?", "answers": ["A `for` loop that listens for browser events.", "A model of concurrency that handles asynchronous operations. It consists of the call stack, the message queue, and the microtask queue.", "A JavaScript debugging tool.", "A method for creating custom events."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "The event loop is fundamental to JavaScript's non-blocking nature. It continuously checks if the call stack is empty and, if it is, pushes the next message from the queue to the stack for execution." },
        { "question": "What is the difference between `call()`, `apply()`, and `bind()`?", "answers": ["They are three ways to define a function.", "They are methods used to set the `this` value inside a function, regardless of how it is called.", "They are used for mathematical operations.", "There is no functional difference, only syntax."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "`call()` and `apply()` invoke the function immediately, with `call()` accepting a list of arguments and `apply()` accepting an array of arguments. `bind()` returns a new function with `this` bound to a specific value, which can be called later." },
        { "question": "What is memoization?", "answers": ["A way to remember user preferences.", "An optimization technique where the results of expensive function calls are cached and returned when the same inputs occur again.", "A process of clearing the browser's memory.", "A security feature to prevent unauthorized access."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Memoization is a specific form of caching used to speed up computer programs by storing the results of expensive function calls and returning the cached result when the same inputs are supplied again." },
        { "question": "What is a Web Worker?", "answers": ["A JavaScript library for UI components.", "A script that runs in the background, separate from the main execution thread, to perform long-running tasks without blocking the UI.", "A person who works on web development.", "A security protocol for websites."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Web Workers are a simple means for web content to run scripts in background threads. The worker thread can perform tasks without interfering with the user interface, making the page more responsive." },
        { "question": "What are Service Workers?", "answers": ["A type of Web Worker that acts as a proxy server between the web app, the browser, and the network.", "Customer service representatives for web applications.", "A JavaScript framework.", "A tool for testing website performance."], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "Service Workers enable features like offline capabilities, push notifications, and background data synchronization. They are a key technology behind Progressive Web Apps (PWAs)." },
        { "question": "What is tree shaking?", "answers": ["A CSS animation that makes elements shake.", "A term for the process of removing unused code (dead-code elimination) from the final bundle in modern JavaScript bundlers like Webpack or Rollup.", "A debugging technique for the DOM tree.", "A way to organize files in a project."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Tree shaking relies on ES6 module syntax (`import` and `export`) to determine which parts of a library are being used and which can be safely discarded, leading to smaller bundle sizes." },
        { "question": "What are higher-order functions?", "answers": ["Functions that are more important than others.", "Functions that operate on other functions, either by taking them as arguments or by returning them.", "Functions used in advanced mathematics.", "The main functions in a JavaScript program."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Higher-order functions are a core concept of functional programming. Common examples in JavaScript are `map`, `filter`, and `reduce`." },
        { "question": "What is the difference between Shadow DOM and Virtual DOM?", "answers": ["They are the same thing.", "Shadow DOM is a browser technology for encapsulation, while Virtual DOM is a concept implemented by libraries like React for performance optimization.", "Virtual DOM is more secure than Shadow DOM.", "Shadow DOM is a newer version of the Virtual DOM."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Shadow DOM provides a way to scope CSS and JavaScript to a specific part of the page. Virtual DOM is a programming concept where a virtual representation of the UI is kept in memory and synced with the 'real' DOM, which helps React to do efficient updates." }
      ]
    ]
  },
  "python": {
    "easy": [
      [ // Set 1
        { "question": "What is the correct way to print 'Hello, World!' in Python?", "answers": ["console.log('Hello, World!');", "System.out.println('Hello, World!');", "printf('Hello, World!');", "print('Hello, World!')"], "correctAnswerIndex": 3, "explanation": "The `print()` function is the standard way to output text to the console in Python." },
        { "question": "How do you start a single-line comment in Python?", "answers": ["//", "/* */", "#", "<!-- -->"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "In Python, the hash symbol '#' is used to start a comment that extends to the end of the line." },
        { "question": "Which of these is NOT a built-in data type in Python?", "answers": ["list", "tuple", "dict", "array"], "correctAnswerIndex": 3, "explanation": "While Python has lists, which are array-like, a dedicated 'array' type must be imported from a module like 'array' or 'numpy'." },
        { "question": "What is the result of `10 / 3` in Python 3?", "answers": ["3", "3.0", "3.333...", "Error"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "In Python 3, the '/' operator performs float division, resulting in a floating-point number. For integer division, you would use '//' (which would result in 3)." },
        { "question": "How do you define a function in Python?", "answers": ["function my_function():", "def my_function():", "void my_function():", "define my_function():"], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Functions in Python are defined using the `def` keyword, followed by the function name, parentheses, and a colon." },
        { "question": "What is used to define a block of code (e.g., in a function or loop) in Python?", "answers": ["Curly braces {}", "Parentheses ()", "Indentation", "Keywords 'begin' and 'end'"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Python uses whitespace (indentation) to define code blocks, which is a key feature of its syntax. Inconsistent indentation will cause errors." },
        { "question": "How do you get the length of a list named `my_list`?", "answers": ["my_list.length()", "length(my_list)", "size(my_list)", "len(my_list)"], "correctAnswerIndex": 3, "explanation": "The built-in `len()` function returns the number of items in an object, such as a list, tuple, or string." },
        { "question": "Which statement is used to make a decision in Python?", "answers": ["if", "for", "while", "def"], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "The `if` statement, along with `elif` and `else`, is used to execute code conditionally." },
        { "question": "How do you create a list in Python?", "answers": ["my_list = {\"a\", \"b\", \"c\"}", "my_list = (\"a\", \"b\", \"c\")", "my_list = [\"a\", \"b\", \"c\"]", "my_list = <\"a\", \"b\", \"c\">"], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Lists are created using square brackets `[]`, and they are mutable, meaning their contents can be changed." },
        { "question": "What is the logical 'AND' operator in Python?", "answers": ["&&", "&", "AND", "and"], "correctAnswerIndex": 3, "explanation": "Python uses the English words `and`, `or`, and `not` for logical operations." }
      ]
    ],
    "medium": [
      [ // Set 1
        { "question": "What is a 'list comprehension'?", "answers": ["A way to understand lists.", "A concise way to create lists from iterables.", "A built-in function for sorting lists.", "A special type of list that cannot be modified."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "List comprehensions provide a shorter and more readable syntax for creating a new list based on the values of an existing list. Example: `[x*x for x in range(10)]`" },
        { "question": "What is the difference between a list and a tuple?", "answers": ["Lists are mutable, while tuples are immutable.", "Tuples are mutable, while lists are immutable.", "They are the same, just with different syntax.", "Lists can only hold numbers, tuples can hold strings."], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "This is the key difference. Once a tuple is created, you cannot change its elements, whereas you can add, remove, or change elements in a list." },
        { "question": "What is a dictionary in Python?", "answers": ["A collection of words.", "An ordered collection of items.", "An unordered collection of key-value pairs.", "A built-in spell checker."], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Dictionaries are used to store data values in key:value pairs. They are optimized for retrieving data when you know the key." },
        { "question": "What does the `if __name__ == \"__main__\":` block do?", "answers": ["It's the only way to run a Python script.", "It defines the main function of the program.", "The code inside this block will only run when the script is executed directly (not when it's imported as a module).", "It checks if the script is running on the main computer."], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "This is a standard idiom in Python that allows a script to be used as both a reusable module and a standalone program." },
        { "question": "How do you handle exceptions in Python?", "answers": ["Using `try...catch` blocks.", "Using `if...error` statements.", "Using `try...except` blocks.", "Python does not have exception handling."], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "You place the code that might raise an error in the `try` block, and the code to handle the error in the `except` block." },
        { "question": "What is a Python module?", "answers": ["A single line of Python code.", "A file containing Python definitions and statements.", "A built-in data type.", "A comment in the code."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Modules allow you to logically organize your Python code. Grouping related code into a module makes the code easier to understand and use." },
        { "question": "What is PIP?", "answers": ["A code formatting tool.", "A Python Integrated Playground.", "The standard package manager for Python.", "A version control system."], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "PIP (Pip Installs Packages) is a command-line tool that allows you to install and manage libraries and dependencies that are not part of the standard library." },
        { "question": "How do you open a file named `data.txt` for reading in Python?", "answers": ["file = open(\"data.txt\", \"r\")", "file = read(\"data.txt\")", "file = open.file(\"data.txt\")", "file = new File(\"data.txt\")"], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "The `open()` function is the standard way to interact with files. The second argument, 'r', specifies the mode (read). It's best practice to use a `with open(...)` block to ensure the file is automatically closed." },
        { "question": "What is a 'set' in Python?", "answers": ["An ordered collection of unique items.", "An unordered collection of unique items.", "A collection that allows duplicate items.", "Another name for a list."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Sets are useful when you need to store unique items and perform mathematical set operations like union, intersection, and difference." },
        { "question": "What is `*args` and `**kwargs` in a function definition?", "answers": ["They are required parameters for every function.", "They are used for pointer arithmetic.", "They allow a function to accept a variable number of positional arguments (`*args`) and keyword arguments (`**kwargs`).", "They are used to import modules."], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "`*args` collects extra positional arguments into a tuple, and `**kwargs` collects extra keyword arguments into a dictionary." }
      ]
    ],
    "hard": [
      [ // Set 1
        { "question": "What is a decorator in Python?", "answers": ["A design pattern that adds new functionality to an existing object without modifying its structure.", "A way to style text in the console.", "A special type of comment.", "A built-in data structure."], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "Decorators are functions that take another function as an argument, add some functionality, and return another function. They are syntactically represented with the '@' symbol and are often used for logging, timing, and access control." },
        { "question": "What is the Global Interpreter Lock (GIL)?", "answers": ["A security feature that prevents unauthorized code execution.", "A mutex that allows only one thread to execute Python bytecode at a time in the CPython interpreter.", "A tool for debugging multi-threaded applications.", "A way to lock global variables."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "The GIL simplifies memory management in CPython but means that multi-threaded, CPU-bound Python programs may not see a performance increase from using multiple processor cores. It's not a problem for I/O-bound programs." },
        { "question": "What is the difference between `.py` and `.pyc` files?", "answers": ["`.py` files are for Python 2, `.pyc` for Python 3.", "`.py` contains source code, while `.pyc` contains the compiled bytecode of the source code.", "`.pyc` files are configuration files.", "There is no difference."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "When a module is imported, the Python interpreter compiles the source code into bytecode and saves it as a `.pyc` file to speed up subsequent imports of the same module." },
        { "question": "What are generators in Python?", "answers": ["Functions that can be paused and resumed, generating a sequence of values over time.", "A library for creating random numbers.", "A class that generates objects.", "A tool for automatic code generation."], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "Generators are created using functions with the `yield` keyword. They are memory-efficient for working with large sequences because they produce items one at a time, only when needed, rather than creating the entire sequence in memory at once." },
        { "question": "What is monkey-patching?", "answers": ["A way to fix bugs in third-party libraries.", "The dynamic modification of a class or module at runtime.", "A debugging technique.", "A type of performance optimization."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Monkey-patching refers to changing the behavior of a class or module at runtime, often by replacing a method or attribute. It can be powerful but also dangerous, as it can lead to code that is hard to understand and maintain." },
        { "question": "What is the difference between `__str__` and `__repr__`?", "answers": ["`__str__` should return a user-friendly, readable representation of an object, while `__repr__` should return an unambiguous, official representation (ideally one that can be used to recreate the object).", "`__repr__` is for strings, `__str__` is for numbers.", "There is no difference.", "`__str__` is the old version, `__repr__` is the new version."], "correctAnswerIndex": 0, "explanation": "`print()` and `str()` use `__str__`. The interactive console and `repr()` use `__repr__`. If `__str__` is not defined, `__repr__` is used as a fallback." },
        { "question": "What are context managers and the `with` statement?", "answers": ["A way to manage global variables.", "An object that defines the methods `__enter__` and `__exit__`, used with the `with` statement to manage resources like file handles or network connections.", "A tool for managing virtual environments.", "A syntax for creating multi-line strings."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "The `with` statement ensures that cleanup code in the `__exit__` method is always executed, even if errors occur within the block. This is a robust way to handle resource setup and teardown." },
        { "question": "What are metaclasses in Python?", "answers": ["Classes that are more important than others.", "Classes whose instances are also classes.", "A feature for creating private classes.", "A deprecated feature from Python 2."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "Metaclasses are an advanced concept that allows you to control how classes are created. The default metaclass is `type`. By creating your own metaclass, you can inject or modify behavior at the time of class creation, which is used in frameworks like Django and SQLAlchemy." },
        { "question": "How does inheritance work in Python, including multiple inheritance?", "answers": ["Python does not support inheritance.", "A class can inherit from a single parent class only.", "A class can inherit attributes and methods from one or more parent classes.", "Inheritance is only for built-in types."], "correctAnswerIndex": 2, "explanation": "Python supports multiple inheritance. When a method is called, Python uses the Method Resolution Order (MRO) to determine which parent class's method to use if there are conflicts." },
        { "question": "What is Duck Typing?", "answers": ["A style of programming where you must explicitly declare the type of every variable.", "A concept where the type or the class of an object is less important than the methods it defines.", "A naming convention for Python variables.", "A debugging tool for type errors."], "correctAnswerIndex": 1, "explanation": "The saying is: 'If it walks like a duck and it quacks like a duck, then it must be a duck.' In Python, this means you don't care about an object's specific type, only whether it has the methods or attributes you need to perform an operation." }
      ]
    ]
  }
}

    